&gt;&gt; Ladies and gentlemen, please
&gt;&gt;  女士们 先生们
welcome Vice President of
让我们欢迎
Platform Technologies, Andreas
负责技术平台开发的副总裁
Wendker.
Andreas Wendker
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Good afternoon.
&gt;&gt;  下午好
Welcome to WWDC.
欢迎来到 WWDC
As you heard this morning in the
大家今天上午在主题演讲中了解到
keynote, this is a year with a
今年的重点集中在
strong focus on technology
Apple 所有产品线的
fundamentals and refinements
技术基础
across all Apple product lines.
与改良上面
We're introducing numerous APIs
我们推出了很多 API
that enable new use cases for
让你们的 app 能够有新的应用案例
your apps, covering a broad
范围十分广泛
spectrum that ranges from
从机器学习
machine learning to augmented
到增强现实
and virtual reality, to access
与虚拟现实
to the music, to the Apple Music
再到使用 Apple Music
Library.
Library 获取音乐
We're also making improvements
我们还对许多
to many of our core
核心科技做了
technologies.
改良
For example, our new modern file
比如我们的新的现代
system, APFS, is now even more
文件系统 APFS 现在更加
powerful.
强力了
That created a new, much faster
这会带来一个新的  更高效的
version of method, and we helped
版本  此外我们还
define and adopt a new
帮助定义并采用了
high-efficiency image format
带有先进压缩技术的
with advanced compression.
高效图形格式
Now, most of these technologies
大多数技术
and APIs apply to all our
与 API 都适用
operating systems across the
我们所有的操作系统
board, so they're moving forward
所以它们是共同进步的
But let's also take a look at
但我们也要看一下
some specific highlights that
一些独具特色的特点
affect you as software
它们会影响作为应用开发者的
developers.
诸位
iOS 11 has a huge number of
iOS 11 有大量的很棒的功能
incredible features, but perhaps
但也许最重要的是
most importantly, it is the
这是目前为止最大的
biggest iPad release ever, and
iPad 的发布
it turns iPad into a major
iOS11 把 iPad 变成了一个
productivity device with a new
主力生产力设备
Dock, drag and drop, find
有了新的 Dock Drag and Drop
management, and enhanced
查找管理  和增强的
multitasking.
多任务功能
In macOS, you really took the
在 macOS 中 你们花了很多时间去
time to broadly clean up
大范围清理
performance and animations.
动画性能
And for the additional support
现在有了
for Fusion Drives and for disk
对 Fusion Drives 和对磁盘加密的
encryption, APFS is now ready to
附加支持 APFS 已经准备好
come to the Mac as a fully
作为一个全面支持的文件系统
supported file system.
进入 Mac 了
You also laid the groundwork for
你们还做了许多基础工作
turning the Mac into a virtual
让虚拟现实在 Mac 中
reality powerhouse.
大显身手
And for watchOS, you made our UI
在 watchOS 上 你们让我们的
components for flexible so that
UI 组件变得更加灵便
you can create more custom user
这样就可以提供更多的个性化
experiences.
用户体验了
New modes for navigation and
导航与录音的
audio recording allow your apps
新模式会让你们的 app
to continue processing data and
在后台运行的时候
providing feedback to the user,
也可以持续处理数据
even when running in the
并反馈给用户
background.
新的统一的 app 运行时间
keeps your apps more responsive.
让 app 变得更加灵敏
You also added support for Core
你们还为 Core
Bluetooth so that you can now
Bluetooth 增加了支持
directly connect to BTLE devices
现在可以直接连接 BTLE 设备
and display data from them right
并直接在用户的手腕上
on the user's wrist.
显示数据了
And in tvOS, we implemented a
在 tvOS 里  我们提供了
wide variety of enhancements
很多种类的增强
that you can take advantage of
你们可以利用它们
for rounding out your apps'
大大增强 app 的功能
functionality for all your
从而让所有用户受益
users, including right-to-left
其中就包括对一些语言
support for the appropriate
从右向左写作的文字的
languages.
支持
And beyond our operating
在我们的操作系统之外
systems, you're also hard at
你们也努力工作
work on improving our general
改进我们整体的
developer ecosystem and the
开发者生态系统
support they give you for
这个系统能为你们
marketing and shipping apps.
提供 app 的推广与应用
We increased the number of users
我们增加了用户的数量
you can have, and you shipped
而且你们可以通过
beta versions of your apps in
TestFlight 发送你们的 app 的
TestFlight.
Beta 版本
And the App Store now allows you
App Store 现在允许
to rule out updates to your apps
你们在几天的时间里
over a period of several days.
排除掉 app 的更新
You'll be able to respond to
这样就可以对用户的反馈
user feedback, user reviews of
和评论做出反应了
You'll be able to post
你们能够在 Store 页面上
promotional materials on your
展现推广的一些素材
Store pages and much, much more.
还有更多信息
And we are modernizing the
我们还在 App Store 上
content in our App Stores.
的内容方面做了现代化处理
We've been working for a while
我们已经有一段时间在
now on getting all iOS software
致力于让所有的 iOS 软件
to take advantage of the power
能够利用上我们的 64 位处理器
and performance for our 64-bit
的强大性能
With iOS 11, you're completing
有了 iOS 11 你们就可以彻底
this transition.
实现这个变化了
You're going to thin iOS 11 to
iOS 11 只为 64 位的 app
be 64-bit only, and 32-bit apps
提供支持  而 32 位的 app
are not going to be supported
以后就不会被支持了
And with that, it's now time to
现在是时候
turn our attention to doing the
把注意力转向 macOS
same with macOS.
并做同样的事了
The transition to 64-bit-only
让 Mac app 也向 64 位转化
Mac apps is going to take place
这个过程将和 iOS 上的
very similarly to how we handled
转化过程非常相似
Most importantly, High Sierra is
最重要的是 High Sierra
going to be the last macOS
将是最后一个全面支持 32 位 app
release to fully support 32-bit
而没有任何妥协的
apps without compromises.
MacOS 更新了
In the next major release after
在 High Sierra 之后的下一次
High Sierra, you're going to
重大更新的时候
aggressively start warning users
如果你们的 app 不兼容 64 位
if apps are not compatible for
就必须开始对用户提出严重警告
You're updating the Mac App
Mac App Store 也将就此
Store rules accordingly.
作出调整
In about six months, you'll
在大约 6 个月后
require that all new apps
你们将要求所有提交到
submitted to the Mac App Store
Mac App Store 的新 app
will be 64-bit capable and, in a
都必须支持 64 位
year from now, will require all
一年后  所有的新 app
new apps and updates to existing
和现有 app 的更新
apps to be 64-bit only when
在提交到 Mac App Store 的时候
submitted to the Mac App Store.
都必须仅支持 64 位
So for the next 90 minutes or
在接下来的 90 分钟
so, they're going to go deep on
他们将深入讲解
the most important APIs and
我们今天要发布的
technologies that we're
最重要的 API
announcing today.
和技术
They're also going to cover our
还会深入讲解
developer tools in depth.
我们的开发者工具
In fact, they're going to start
实际上  他们首先会讲到
with Swift Playgrounds.
Swift Playgrounds
I'm going to hand it over to
我现在要把舞台交给
Matthew [inaudible] for that.
Matthew 请他讲解
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Andreas.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Andreas
Swift Playgrounds has brought
Swift Playgrounds 为教育
something new and important to
带来了一些新的  重要的变化
education -- teaching
那就是用真正的代码
programming to kids in a fun way
以充满乐趣的方式
using real code.
教孩子们编程
And the response has been
反响
tremendous.
非常良好
After less than ten months on
在 App Store 上发布不到 10 个月
the App Store, over one million
就已经有超过一千万人
people have started to code with
开始用 Swift Playgrounds
Swift Playgrounds.
进行编程了
And these users are from all
用户来自世界各地
over the world, as we made the
因为我们在 6 个国家及地区
app and content available in six
发布了这个 app  做了相应的本地化处理
In fact, almost two-thirds of
实际上  所有用户中
these users are from outside the
有大约三分之二
United States, making Swift
不是美国人  这让 Swift
Playgrounds an international
Playgrounds  获得了国际性的
success.
成功
Since our first release last
去年首发以来
year, we've added a number of
我们先后向这个 app
new features to the application,
加入了一系列新特性
such as line-by-line
比如在代码运行时
highlighting of your code as
一行行的高光显示
it's running, content
新内容可用时
notifications when new content's
出现内容通知
available, and the ability to
以及添加新的
add new Playground pages.
Playground  页面功能
These features and others
这些特性以及许多其他特性
alongside new content has given
和新内容一起使
Swift Playgrounds fantastic
Swift Playgrounds 变得出色
Now, as you may have already
大家也许听说了
heard, today we're making a new
今天我们要发布
version of Swift Playgrounds
Swift Playgrounds 的新版本
available, version 1.5.
也就是1.5版
And in this release, we're
在这次发布中
making it easier for users to
我们会让用户更容易连接
connect to Bluetooth robots,
蓝牙机器人
drones, and devices.
无人机等设备
And this takes Swift out into
这会让 Swift 进入
the real world, venturing even
真正的世界  甚至可以
outdoors.
出门去探索
And it harmonizes naturally as
它会随着你的编程技巧提高
your programming skills evolve.
自然地予以配合
Now, with this release, we have
在这次发布中
worked with some amazing
我们与一些出色的伙伴
partners who also wanted to
合作  他们也想利用 Swift
design great experiences for
为他们的设备
their devices using Swift, like
设计很好的体验
Parrot with their mini-drones
比如 Parrot 公司的迷你无人机
who can fly and flip, UBTECH
可以飞行和翻转  还有 UBTECH
with their buildable and
可搭建  可编程的 MeeBot
programmable MeeBot, Sphero with
还有 Sphero 的
their dynamic Sprk+ robotic
Sprk+ 机器球 非常厉害
ball, Wonder Workshop and the
还有 Wonder Workshop 的
racing and talking Dash,
能够行走和说话的 Dash
Skoogmusic and their Tactile
还有 Skoogmusic 和他们的 Tactile
Musical cube, and MINDSTORMS EV3
Musical cube 还有乐高公司的
by LEGO.
MINDSTORMS EV3
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
The limitless possibilities you
你可以用 MINDSTORMS
can build with MINDSTORMS make
搭建出无穷的可能
it a perfect pairing with Swift
这让它和 Swift Playgrounds 成为
Playgrounds.
绝配
In fact, all of our partners
实际上 我们所有的伙伴
have truly embraced the
都运用了这个 app 的
interactivity of the app,
互动性
designing intuitive APIs you can
设计出直观的  可以拖拽放置的 API
drag and drop and presenting
并在 live view 中
up-to-date device and sensor
推出最新的设备
data in the live view.
和传感数据
And this combination is truly
在你看到你的想法
captivating as you see your
变成代码并让设备活起来
thoughts become code and bring
这个过程非常
devices to life.
让人着迷
Now, all of our partners have
现在  我们所有的伙伴
designed Playgrounds to work
都做到了让 Playgrounds
with their devices, and you can
和他们的设备共同工作
find them in the new Accessories
你可以在 app 里的新设备
tab of the app, where there are
菜单找到它们
samples to play with and
有可以试玩的样品
templates to create your own
还有建立你自己的文件的
file.
模板
And we are truly eager to see
我们很期待看到
how users of all ages take
不同年龄的用户
advantage of the new Swift
利用新的 Swift
Playgrounds because we believe
Playgrounds 因为我们相信
it is the best way to control
它是用你自己写的代码
robots and drones with code you
控制机器人和无人机
write yourself.
最棒的工具
The new version of Swift
Swift Playgrounds 的新版本
Playgrounds is available today
今天就能在 App Store 里
for free in the App Store, and
免费下载
you can find many of the
你可以在你附近的 Apple 实体店
Bluetooth accessories from our
找到很多我们的合作伙伴
partners at an Apple Store near
生产的蓝牙设备
Now, there's another version of
今天我还想和大家分享
Swift Playgrounds I'd like to
另一个版本的 Swift Playgrounds
share with you today, and that's
那就是 Swift Playgrounds 2
Swift Playgrounds 2, shipping
这个版本将会在今年秋天的
later this fall.
晚些时候发布
Today, we have engaging content,
今天 我们的内容包括
like our Learn to Code series,
代码学习
challenges, and the new
存在的挑战  以及来自合作伙伴的
Playgrounds from our partners,
新升级版本的 Playgrounds
but we also know that you have
但我们也知道  你们也有
many inspired ideas too, so this
很多很棒的想法
fall, we're going to make it
所以今年秋天
easy for everyone to share
我们会让每个人更容易分享
Playgrounds.
Playgrounds
With Swift Playgrounds 2, we
有了 Swift Playgrounds 2
will support feeds of
我们就能够支持
third-party content that users
第三方内容的信息流
can subscribe to.
用户可以订阅
And this content makes it really
这个内容会让
easy for schools to host
学校开办课程
curriculum, developers to post
开发者发布 API 探索
API explorations, and friends
朋友之间分享想法
have a simple way to share
让这些事变得更容易
This release will also include
这个版本还会包括
an integrated documentation
升级的文件编制体验
experience, support for Swift 4
在 iOS11 SDK 中支持 Swift 4
in the iOS 11SDK, and enable the
并启动相机功能
use of camera and augmented
和增强现实 API
And we're going to extend global
我们还会增强
reach of the application by
这个 app 的国际性
adding in localizations for
再提供 8 个语言的
eight additional languages.
本地化版本
Beta versions of Swift
Swift Playgrounds 2
Playgrounds 2 will be made
的 beta 版本
available via TestFlight, and
可以在 TestFlight 上获取
you can sign up at
大家可以在
developer.apple.com to try out
developer.apple.com 上登记
these releases.
试着玩一玩
So two big versions of Swift
所以我们为你准备了两个
Playgrounds for you.
Swift Playgrounds 的重要版本
I'd like to switch topics and
现在我想换个话题
start talking about Xcode 9.
说一说 Xcode 9
Xcode 9 is a major release.
Xcode 9 也是一个重大发布
We have made significant
我们在各项工具的基础
investments in our foundations,
工作流程和性能
work flows, and performance
上面都做了重大投入
across the tools with some
并且已经获得了一些
pretty substantial results.
可喜的成果
I'd like to start today by
今天我想先讲一讲
talking about our Source Editor.
我们在 Xcode 9 里的
In Xcode 9, we have completely
Source Editor
re-implemented our Source
我们彻底重新实现了 Source
Editor.
Editor
It's been rewritten from the
用 Swift 彻底重写了它
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
And I agree.
我同意
It's a pretty big deal.
这是件大事
So at first glance, you'll see
第一眼看去
the familiar crisp presentation
你会看到熟悉的
of multiple fonts and weights,
多种字体和字号
but now with more options for
但现在有更多选项
line spacing, cursor types, and
可以用于行距  光标类型
more.
等等
And we took the notion of
我们还采用了
semantic presentation and didn't
语义表达的概念  并没有
stop at source code because we
停止在源代码阶段  因为
now have an integrated Markdown
现在我们有统一的
editor as well.
Markdown 编辑器了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
In addition to stylized editing,
此外  针对城市化编辑
you'll find the familiar editor
你们会有类似的编辑
experiences, like using the Jump
经历  例如使用 Jump bar
bar for navigation,
进行导航  在链接上
Command-clicking on links, even
使用 Command-clicking on links
using Edit All in Scope to
甚至是在 Scope 里用 Edit All
change references.
来更改 reference
Now, when you start working with
现在  你开始编写源代码时
your source code, you'll find
你会发现 issues
that issues now display smartly,
现在得到了漂亮的显示
no longer adjusting the layout
不再需要调整
of your code.
代码的布局了
Issues now include more detail
Issues 现在有更多细节了
-- yep.
没错
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Issues now display with more
Issues 现在能够以更多细节显示
detail and have the Fix-it work
并且集成了 Fix-it
flow integrated right alongside,
工作流
including the ability to apply
包括一键使用
multiple Fix-its with a single
多个 Fix-its 的功能
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
And this new issue presentation
这个新的 issue 展示
is the perfect canvas for the
是一块完美的画布  适用于
over 300 new diagnostics,
超过 300 个新诊断程式
analyzers, and Fix-its we've
分析器  和我们为了
added to help you all write
帮你们写出更棒的代码而添加的
great code.
Fix-its
Now, performance is also
性能也很重要
important, and in this release,
在这次发布后
you'll find the editor opens
你会发现编辑器打开文件
files three times faster, you'll
速度比以前快 3 倍
find smooth scrolling at 60
在文件中浏览时
frames per second as you move
以每秒 60 帧的速度滚动
about the file, and jumping to
效果也会更顺畅
lines is 50 times faster than
跳到某一行的速度则比以前提高了
before.
50 倍
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
To put it simply, everything
简单来说
happens instantaneously.
一切都会在瞬间完成
Now, the editing experience is
现在  在 Xcode 9 中的编辑体验
also new in Xcode 9.
也会是全新的
Our editor now has more semantic
我们的编辑器现在有了更多的
awareness, and we've brought
语义意识  我们还使用了
over the tokenized editing
从 Swift Playgrounds 那里
experience from Swift
带来的标记化编辑
Playgrounds.
体验
As you move about your source,
你在代码中移动的时候
we're going to highlight the
我们会把下面的结构
structure underneath.
高亮标出
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
And when you click on one of the
你点击其中一个标记时
tokens, we're going to present
会出现一个
an Action menu full of symbolic
充满符号性变化的
transformations to help you
动作菜单帮你
evolve your code.
扩展你的代码
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
And I'm guessing some of you
我猜有人已经猜到
know where this is going next.
接下来我会说什么了
And yes, it is true.
没错  是真的
Xcode 9 has a brand-new
Xcode 9 有一个全新的
refactoring system for it.
重构系统了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Indeed. Our refactoring system
没错  我们的重构系统
works with Swift, Objective-C,
适用于 Swift  Objective-C
C, and C++, so you can use it
C 和 C++ 所以你可以
throughout your projects.
尽情使用
And the refactoring work flow
重构工作流
takes advantage of the new
能够利用新的
tokenized editing experience to
标记化编辑体验
present contextual actions, like
代表 contextual actions
Extract and Rename, and all of
比如抽取和重命名
these actions are bindable, so
这些都是可绑定的
you can set key equivalents for
你可以把常用的动作设成
ones you use frequently.
关键性的量值
And we also have a gorgeous
我们也准备了一个很棒的
presentation to help you review
演示来帮大家熟悉这些改动
And to show you what this is
所以下面我要
like, I'd like to bring up Ken
请 Ken Orr 上台
Orr to give you a demonstration
为大家演示
of the new Source Editor with
重构的新 Source Editor
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Matthew.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Matthew
So Xcode 9 has a brand-new
Xcode 9 有了一个全新的
Source Editor rewritten from the
彻底重写的 Source Editor
ground up to be fast, and I
它变得更快了
think speed is one of the very
我想你首先就会注意到
first things you'll notice.
这种速度的变化
Scrolling in this 10,000-line
在这 1 万行代码
file is super smooth all the way
中一直滚动到底  都非常
down to the bottom, and I can
顺畅  而且我可以
just instantly right back to the
瞬间回到顶部
And of course, code, it looks
当然  代码看上去
absolutely gorgeous.
也棒极了
Let me make that a little bit
我把它放大一点
bigger so it's easier for you to
让大家看得更容易
see.
点击几下 Command+
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
It's the little things, right.
这都是小改动
So my project here is an iOS
假设我正在制作一个 iOS app
app, and it lets users explore
让我们的用户探索
our solar system.
太阳系
And I want to add a little bit
我想加几行
of code.
代码
I'm going to jump over to this
我要跳转到这个
Objective-C file, and this bit
Objective-C 文件上
of code that I just added, it
而我刚加入的这几行代码
has a small problem.
有一点小问题
So first off, you can see the
你会看到 这个新的
brand-new issues presentation,
issues presentation 马上出现了
and it's got Fix-its built right
而且还内置了 Fix-its
Now, this particular issue is
这个在 Objective-C 是新的
warning me that I'm using iOS 11
而且还警告我  我是在用 iOS 11
API, but my project here, it
API  但我的 project
deploys back to iOS X, where
却是配置到 iOS 10 的
this would crash [applause].
这会导致系统崩溃 [掌声]
And this issue has a Fix-it,
对于这个问题有 Fix-it
which I'll accept.
我会接受
And when I do, Xcode wraps my
如果我接受了 Xcode 就会用新的
code using the new Objective-C
Objective-C 关键词 atAvailable
keyword, atAvailable.
把我的代码打包
So now, that little bit of code,
现在  这几行代码
it'll only run on iOS 11.
就只会在 iOS 11 下面才运行了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声]
There's another new Fix-it I
我还想展示另外一个
want to show you.
新的 Fix-it
I'm going to jump over to this
我要跳到这边这个
SWF file here.
SWF 文件上面
This is the class that
这个 class 代表的是
represents a moon in our solar
我们的太阳系中的一个
system, and I'm going to adopt
卫星  我要使用
the physics body protocol.
物理物体协议
It's got a few different
这有一些不同的
methods.
方法
Whoops. It's got a few different
我有一些
methods that I need to
不同的方法
implement.
当然  我还没有执行
them yet, so I get an issue.
因此出现了一个问题
And now, with just one click on
现在  只要点击一下
the single Fix-it, it'll add all
Fix-it 它就会把所有
the methods that I haven't yet
我还没有执行的方法
implemented.
添加进来
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So Xcode 9 can also help me
Xcode 9 还能帮助我
transform and refactor my code.
转化并重构我的代码
So let me show you that.
我来展示一下
I'm going to jump over to this
我现在要跳到这个
solarsystem.swf file and I'm
solarsystem.swf 文件上
going to hold down the Command
按住 Command 键
key and move my mouse.
操作鼠标
And when I do, Xcode shows me
这时 Xcode 就会显示出
the structure of my code.
我的代码的结构
When I click, I get a set of
点击一下  就能得到
options and transformations that
一系列选项与变化
are specific to the expression
这是针对我所点击的
that I clicked on.
Expression 的
So here I clicked on an
我在这里点击这个
expression that's creating a
expression 生成一个
moon object and then adding that
卫星  然后把它加到
to the Earth.
地球上
And, you know, I actually
你知道  我个人更喜欢
personally prefer to capture all
捕捉我在
the objects I create in
变量中生成的所有对象
variables, so I'm just going to
所以我就把这个提取出来
extract this out into an
进入一个 expression
expression, and I'll use Edit
然后我使用 Scope 里的 Edit All
All in Scope to give this a
来给它起个好名字
better name, Luna.
月球
And, you know, while we're at
大家知道  实际上
it, actually, I like my methods
我喜欢让 methods
to be short and to the point, so
简短并直达主题
I think I'm going to pull out
因此我要把这个
this If block into its own
If block 拉到它自己的
method.
method 里
And when I do, Xcode creates a
我这样做的时候 Xcode 会
new method for me, adds all of
为我生成一个新 method
that code to it, and then leaves
并把所有代码添加进去
me with a call to that method
然后在起始处留给我一个
back where we started.
这个 method 的 call
Let's give that a new name too.
也给它起个名吧
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So those are a couple local
这就是一些本地的
transformations, but a lot of
转换  但很多时候
times what I want to do, I want
我想做的是
to refactor the name of
重构在整个 project 里面
something that's used throughout
使用的东西
my entire project.
的名字
In fact, I've got a great
实际上  我这就有个很好的
candidate for that here -- this
例子  也就是这个
position method.
position method
That's kind of a generic name.
这个名字有点一般
I think I could come up with
我想我应该把它
something a little bit more
换成一个更具描述性的
descriptive.
名字
So I'm going to hold down the
所以我就要按住
Command key, click, say
Command 键  点击  并说
"rename," and when I do, Xcode
重命名  这时
folds down the file that I'm
Xcode 就会收起我所在的文件
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Folds down that file and it
收起这个文件
pulls in slices from across my
然后从我的 project 各个
project where I'm using that
使用了这个 method 的地方
method.
把它们拉上来
So I'll pick a new name here.
我选个新名字
Let's go with something like
就用这个吧
"orbital position."
"orbital position"
As I type, it updates live
我键入的时候
across all those slides.
它就会把所有的 slide 都改名了
I can rename parameter names
我还可以为参数
too.
重命名
First parameter name, that seems
第一个参数名  看上去
OK.
没问题
Instead of "date" for the second
但第二个名称 date
one, I'll with something like
我决定把它改成
"moment in time."
"moment in time"
Click Rename, and that's it.
点击重命名  完成了
So rename factoring works great
所以对于这样的 method
for methods like this.
重命名这个重构是很好用的
Also works for classes too.
对于所有的 classes 的工作也是一样
So up here I've got this class,
在这里有这个 class
"trans-Neptunian object."
"trans-Neptunian object"
That's kind of a mouthful, so
这名字有点太长了
let's give that a little bit
我们给它改一个简单点的
simpler name.
名字吧
I'm going to rename this guy
我要把它的名字改成
"minor planet."
"minor planet"
So refactoring, it works for
重构  它能够完成
everything you'd expect.
你所希望的一切
In my project here, that means
在我的 project 里  它意味着
SWF files, Objective-C files,
SWF 文件 Objective-C 文件
and even storyboards.
甚至是故事板
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
When I'm done, click Rename, and
我做好后  点击重命名
that's it.
就完工了
Really simple.
非常简单
Really powerful.
非常好用
That's the new Source Editor and
这就是新的 Source Editor
refactoring in Xcode 9.
和 Xcode 9 里的重构功能
Matthew?
Matthew 上来吧
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Ken.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Ken
I told you it was gorgeous.
非常精彩的讲解
So new refactoring is a great
新的重构功能
way to evolve your code.
大大有利于改进你的代码
In addition to the rename
除了重命名
refactoring, we're also going to
这项重构  我们还会加入
include a number of local
一系列本地转化
transformations, like extract,
比如抽取代码
adding missing overrides, and
添加 missing overrides
working with localized strings.
以及本地化的字符串
But this is just the beginning
但这只是开始
because we're going to be open
因为我们会公开重构引擎
sourcing the refactoring engine
的源代码  这是
as part of the Apple, Clang, and
Apple Clang 和 Swift compilers
Swift compilers.
的一部分
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Xcode will automatically pick up
Xcode 会自动拾取
transformations you build in
你在本地工具链中
local toolchains, so you have a
搭建的转换这样你就
great way to prototype new
有一个很棒的方法去让你的新的转换原型化
So our new Source Editor --
我们的新 Source Editor
great look and feel, awesome
看上去很棒
performance, and now with
性能更是强大  现在又能
refactoring.
重构了
A great start to Xcode 9.
这是 Xcode 9 的一个良好开端
And we also have some big news
我们在 Swift 里
in Swift, and for that, I'd like
也有一些好消息
to bring up Ted Kremenek to tell
下面就请 Ted Kremenek
you more.
来讲解
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; With Swift, we set out on a
&gt;&gt;  对于 Swift
mission to make programming
我们的任务是让编程
easier, faster, safer, and more
更简单  更快速  更安全  更现代化
And in a little less than three
在不到三年的时间里
years, the pace of adoption
改进的速度是
remains phenomenal.
十分惊人的
In that time, over 250,000 apps
在这段时间里  超过 25 万个 app
have been written in Swift and
的代码是用 Swift 写就的并
submitted to the App Store.
提交到 App Store 上面
And it's not just the number of
不仅是这个数量
apps that's exciting.
令人振奋
It's that companies are building
科技公司真的是
apps in Swift that they really
在用 Swift 写那些他们
do depend on.
赖以生存的 app
And beyond the App Store,
在 App Store 之外
enterprise and business have
公司和企业也都
also embraced Swift.
接受了 Swift
IBM has authored more than 100
IBM 用 Swift 写了
of their MobileFirst iOS apps in
100多个 MobileFirst iOS 系统的 app
Swift, and both IBM and SAP have
IBM 和 SAP 都发布了
released SDKs that allow Swift
允许 Swift 开发者
developers to take advantage of
利用他们的服务基础设施的
their services infrastructure.
SDK
So we're thrilled at how Swift
我们对于 Swift 的表现
has been doing, but Swift, of
非常满意  当然
course, isn't standing still.
Swift 不会停滞不前
Xcode 9 includes a new release
Xcode 9 包括新发布的
of Swift, Swift 4, and we're
Swift 和 Swift 4
excited about what it brings.
我们对此很期待
Now, the focus of this release
这次发布的焦点
really is on the core
是最基础最核心的东西
fundamentals, getting those rock
让这些变得更加坚实可靠
solid, because we want Swift to
因为我们希望 Swift 成为
be a great foundation for
大家搭建软件的
everyone to build their software
最佳基础工具
And so just, I'll be able to
我只能够讲到
touch on just a few of the
这次发布的一小部分
things in this release, but we
内容  但我想
think these are just great
这些应该算是
improvements across the board.
很了不起的改进了
The first thing I want to talk
首先我想说的
about is a vastly improved
是有了极大改进的
string.
字符串
String is, string processing is
字符串处理是
a fundamental aspect of just
写软件的一个
writing software, right.
最基础的方面
We work with strings all the
我们时刻都要和它打交道
And we've always had the goal
我们的目标一直是
that string processing in Swift
让 Swift 里的字符串处理
is first in class without
成为第一类的
compromising on Unicode
而不必向 Unicode correctness
correctness.
有所妥协
And so we've made three
所以我们在 Swift 4 中
important strides towards this
为了这个目标
goal in Swift 4.
迈出了三大步
First, you want to make the API
第一  你想让 API 变得
a lot easier to use, right,
更加易用  对吧
because you're using string all
因为你时刻都在用它
We also wanted to double down on
我们也想大力
improving fidelity with Unicode.
改进 Unicode 的精确度
This is something that string
这一点是字符串
has been good at, but it's not
擅长的  但还没有完全
entirely where we wanted it to
达到我们的期望
be, and we wanted to make
我们想让字符串
strings really fast.
变得超快速
So it's not hard to look at it
所以不难理解
for opportunities of how we
我们当然很希望
wanted to make string easier to
让字符串也变得
use, right.
更加易用
So here's some fragments of code
这里是一些你们可能
that you may have written in
在 Swift 3 里
Swift 3 when you're working with
用字符串写过的代码
string, like iterating over the
比如遍历字符
characters, or querying to see
或者查询字符串
if a string has a given
看看里面是否有某个
character, or stitching strings
字符  或者把字符串
together.
拼接在一起
And what we've found is that we
我们会发现自己要
were frequently reaching down
经常到下面的
for this characters view, right.
这个字符视图上面
I mean, you want to get to the
我是说  你想得到
underlying characters, but it's
基本字符集
one step removed.
但它只有一步之遥
It also creates this unnecessary
它会造成这种不必要的
friction.
麻烦
So in Swift 4, we have vastly
所以在 Swift 4 里  我们极大地
simplified this by removing all
简化了这个过程
this impedance, and now strings
去除了阻碍  现在字符串
are range-replaceable
可以大范围替换
collections of characters.
字符集了
Not only does the code, you
不光是代码会
know, read and write exactly as
完全按你的期望
you would expect, but you have
读写  你还可以把
all the power of generic
集合上的泛型算法的力量
directly on working with
直接用在字符串上
We've also added great syntactic
我们还添加了很棒的句法
[inaudible] such as multi-line
比如多行字符串
string literals, which include,
常量  包括
you know, support for white
White space 语言
String slicing is even more
有了 one-sided ranges 的支持
lightweight with the support
字符切割会变得
from one-sided ranges.
更加不重要
So you could just very nimbly
你可以很快地
specify the fragment of the
在一个片段里
string you want in a slice.
指明你想要的字符串
Now, these improvements to the
这些对于核心人机工程的
core ergonomics also must be
改进必须要得到
accompanied with improvements
Unicode 的改进与支持
And if, when you were working
你在 Swift 3 中
with strings in Swift 3, you may
处理字符串的时候
have noticed some oddities like
应该注意到过
this just kind of leaving you
这样的怪事
wondering, what is going on?
你会想  这是怎么回事
And it really comes down to the
这其实要归因于
richness of Unicode.
Unicode 的丰富性
Our concept of the character is
我们对于字符的概念
actually a composition of
实际上是由多个
multiple Unicode scalar values,
Unicode 标量值构成的
and decomposing these correctly
成功地把它解构
is critical to getting that
对于 Unicode 的精确性
fidelity with Unicode, the
以及字符和字符串 API 的精确性
characters, and the string API.
都至关重要
So in Swift 4, we've moved to
在 Swift 4 中  我们有了
the Unicode 9 Grapheme Breaking
Unicode 9 Grapheme Breaking
algorithm.
算法
It now properly separates these
它能够按照你的期望
strings out or these characters
把这些字符串
out as you would expect, giving
或者字符分离开
you full fidelity with the
让你有基本字符集
underlying character set.
的全面精确度
And this is also really
这真的很重要
important since we're now,
因为字符串就是
strings are collections of
字符的集合
Now, this improvement to Unicode
现在  这个对 Unicode
support has not come at a cost
支持的改进不是以牺牲性能
to performance.
为代价的
We've actually finely-tuned
我们已经调试过
strings implementation.
字符串的运行了
So for most string-processing
所以对大多数的字符串处理工作来说
operations, for English, French,
对于英语  法语
German, Spanish, and really any
德语  西班牙语
language using a Latin-derived
特别是那些以拉丁文为基础的
script, you'll see about a
语言  你会看到
three-and-a-half times
字符串的性能大约
performance improvement for
提高了 3.5 倍
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
And similarly, you see huge
同样 你会看到
improvements working with
简体中文和大部分
simplified Chinese and most
当代日本文字的处理
modern Japanese texts
也有很大改进
[applause].
[掌声]
And that is the improved String
那就是改良后的字符串
-- faster, much easier to use,
更快  更易用
and more powerful.
性能更强
The second feature I want to
我想说的第二个特性
talk about has, is about giving
就是让你们能够
you the ability to easily
轻松把 Swift  类型
convert Swift types to encodable
转化成可编码的格式
formats, like JSON and property
例如 JSON 和属性列表
lists, while adding, providing
同时还提供了
powerful opportunities for
自定义的机会
In Swift, we use both value and
在 Swift 里  我们会用到值类型
reference types, and while
和引用类型
NSCoding supports classes, it
虽然 NSCoding 支持 class
doesn't work at all with structs
但它对 struct 或者 enum 就无能为力了
This new feature works
这个新特性
beautifully with all of them.
能够支持上面所有类型
Let's see this in action.
咱们看一下实际操作
So here I have a simple value
我有一个简单的数值类型
type.
这是一个结构
It's a form.
是一个表
It's got some properties.
有一些属性
And I want to make this
我希望让它能够
encodable and decodable to JSON,
被 JSON 属性列表编码和解码
I could easily do this by adding
我可以轻松做到这点
conformance to a new protocol
只要在一个叫做 Codable 的
called Codable.
新协议里添加一致性就好了
And if the properties of this
如果这个类型的属性
type have types that also
具有与 Codable 一致的类型
conform to Codable, this is
这就是所有
literally all the code I need to
我需要写的代码了
write because the conformance to
因为与这个协议的一致性
this protocol is synthesized by
已经被程序
the compiler.
合成了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So works as you would expect.
它会按照你们的期待工作
I can construct a value of this
我可以建立一个这个类型的值
type, and with a single line of
只需要一行代码
code, I can serialize this out
我便可以把这个序列化到
to JSON.
JSON 上
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
And once I have the JSON value I
一旦我有了 JSON 值
can simply reconstitute it back
就能很轻易地重新建立它
with a single line of code, back
只需一行代码
into a foreign value, and this
让它变回外来值
is also 100% type safe.
这也是 100% 安全的类型
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So simple, easy to use.
非常简单  非常容易
We think you're going to enjoy
我们认为你们一定会爱上它的
it.
Swift 4 里有很多很棒的特性
features in Swift 4, and we've
我们也很满意
also been excited about the
对于 Swift
adoption of Swift.
所做的改进
And so another key goal in Swift
在 Swift 4 中另一个重要的目标
4 is we wanted to make all the
就是我们想让所有的
features easy to adopt.
特性都很容易上手
And that's why in Xcode 9 you
因此在 Xcode 9 里面
can take your Swift 3 projects,
你可以搞定 Swift 3 的项目
open them up, and build them
然后不用做任何修改
with no modifications.
就可以构建它们
This means you can be on the
这意味着你可以使用
latest OS, tools, and even make
最新的 OS 操作系统 工具
use of many of the new language
甚至是很多新的语言特性
features in a release without
而不必更改
having to convert your code.
你的代码
So how does this work?
这要怎么实现呢
In Xcode, there is a build
在 Xcode 里  有一个构建是
setting Swift language version.
设置 Swift 语言版本的功能
It has two values, Swift 3.2 and
它有两个值 Swift 3.2 和
Swift 4.0.
Swift 4.0
What this is is there's one
这意味着
compiler here that supports
一个程序能够支持
these two different language
这两种不同的语言
modes.
模型
And what you can do is you could
你能做的是
have a single project that can
你可以有一个单一项目
mix and match targets that are
混合搭配构建的目标
built, it's either 3.2 or 4.0.
3.2 或者 4.0 都可以
It also means you could have an
还意味着你可以
app that's written using all the
有一个使用全新 Swift 4 特性
new Swift 4 features but uses a
编写的 app 但仍然使用
package or framework that's
Swift 3.2 构建的包
built using Swift 3.2.
或者框架
So it's this extremely easy
这让你会很容易地
on-ramp to taking advantage of
利用最新的 Swift 的
the latest features in Swift.
新特性
So what is Swift 3.2?
Swift 3.2 是什么呢
It's a language mode.
它是个语言模型
You can basically build your
你基本上可以
projects pretty much with no
不做修改  构建你的项目
You can access pretty much all
你可以访问几乎所有
the new language features --
新的语言特性
String, codable, all of them.
字符串  编码  什么都行
You can access all the new APIs
你可以访问在 SDK 上的
from the SDK.
所有 API
The only thing you don't get is
你唯一得不到的是
any Swift-related improvements
在现有的  你以前可能用过的
to existing APIs that you may
API 上  与 Swift 有关的
have been using before.
更新
That's what gives you that easy
因此你不用
onboarding without having to
修改项目就可以
modify your project.
轻松开始
To get those benefits, there's a
要得到这些优势
Swift 4 mode.
这有一个 Swift 4 模型
You have access to essentially
你可以访问几乎
all the new stuff.
所有的新东西
There's also some new
还有很多新机会
opportunities to further improve
去进一步改进
the performance of your app,
你的 app 的性能
including reducing the size of
包括减少
your binaries.
其占用空间
There's a lot of great
对于 Swift 开发者来说
improvements in the SDK for
在 SDK 里也有很多
Swift developers, but to take
很棒的升级
advantage of those, there is
要利用它们
some migration of your code
需要对你的代码做一些
required.
迁移
But these are refinements.
这些是很重要的升级
These are very evolutionary
是革命性的
changes.
改变
And compared to moving from
比起从 Swift 2 到 Swift 3 的
Swift 2 to Swift 3, moving from
大刀阔斧
Swift 3 to Swift 4 is very
从 Swift 3 到 Swift 4 的变化其实很
simple.
简单
Now, we've been thrilled about
我们很开心 大家
the investment everyone has been
对 Swift 投入了这么多精力
making in Swift, and as we've
我们看到这样的
seen that investment grow, so
投入越来越多
have the size of large Swift
Swift 项目的规模也同时
projects, right.
在增长  对吧
People are writing more code in
人们在用 Swift 写更多的代码
And we recognize that this is an
我们意识到这很重要
important area for us to focus
我们需要把力量
our efforts on the tools.
集中到工具改良上
And so we've focused on two key
所以我们致力于两个方面
areas to reduce build times for
来缩短大型项目的
large projects.
构建时间
The first is mix-and-match
首先是混合搭配
Objective-C and Swift projects.
Objective-C 和 Swift 项目
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
By pre-compiling the bridging
通过预编码 bridging header
header, we've seen up to about a
我们在构建时间上获得了
40% improvement in built times,
40% 的提升
particularly for debug builds.
特别是有关 debug 的构建
And we saw this ourselves on
我们在编写自己的
our, compiling our own
音乐 app 上已经见证了这种提升
And similarly, if you're using
同样  如果你在使用
whole-module optimization, we've
全模型优化
vastly improved the utilization
我们极大地提高了程序
of parallelism across the
和构建系统的并行优化
compiler and the build system,
你可以看到
and you can see up to a 2x
构建时间
improvement in build times.
多达2倍的提升
Now, this optimization was so
这个优化非常重要
important that we didn't want to
我们不想等到 Xcode 9 了
hold it back for Xcode 9, and so
因此我们有些激进地
we actually aggressively
在 Xcode 8.3.2
released it in the Xcode 8.3.2.
就发布了
And so many of you have already
因此你们很多人
been experiencing the benefits
都已经体验过这一构建提升
of this build improvement.
带来的好处了
And for those of you who haven't
至于那些还没有
been using whole-module
使用过全模块优化的人
optimization, I encourage you to
我强烈建议你们去
give it a try, given the huge
试一试  因为它真的
wins here.
很厉害
And that is just a taste of some
这些只是 Swift 4 里
of the things in Swift 4.
的冰山一角
We think you're going to enjoy
我们相信你们一定会爱上它
it.
现在我把时间还给
Matthew.
Matthew
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Ted.
&gt;&gt;  多谢 Ted
Another key area of Xcode 9 is
Xcode 的另一个关键特色是
our core technologies, and I'd
我们的核心技术
like to start with our indexers.
我想从索引讲起
Our source and text indexes
我们的源码和文本索引
provide the back end for many
为许多工作流提供了后端支持
work flows, like navigation,
比如导航
searching, and refactoring.
搜索和重构
And in Xcode 9, we have
在 Xcode 9 里
re-architected them to store
我们重新搭建了它们  现在它们
richer data and have improved
可以存储更多数据  性能也更强了
In fact, you'll see work flows,
实际上  你会看到
like Open Quickly runs 35 times
Open Quickly 这样的工作流
faster across your projects.
在你的项目上打开的速度比以前快 35 倍
And searching in large projects
在大型项目中查找速度
is up to 50 times faster.
比以前快 50 倍
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So our new indexers make a huge
所以我们的新的索引真的改变了很多
Additionally, Xcode 9 will
除此之外  Xcode 9 还会
include indexing while building.
在搭建的同时包含索引
Xcode will still index in the
Xcode 同样也会在后台索引
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Xcode will still index in the
Xcode 会在后台索引
background but, when you're
但是  在你构建的时候
building, will take advantage of
它会利用已完成的工作
work already being done to
去生成和
generate and update the index.
更新索引
So when you're done building,
所以在你完成构建后
your index is up to date and all
索引也更新完毕了
the associated functionality is
所有相关功能
available to you quicker than
都以前所未有的快速可以为你所用了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Now, our build system is also a
我们的构建系统
key component and one we've made
也是很关键的
significant investments into to
我们花大力气在它身上
improve performance, add
提升性能
features, and support future
添加特性  让它支持未来的目标
And I'm excited to share with
我很兴奋地与大家分享
you today we have a new build
我们有了一个新的构建系统
Written in Swift, our new build
我们的新构建系统是由 Swift 写成的
system layers on top our open
它在我们的开源
source lower-level build system,
低层级构建系统 llbuild 的上层
llbuild.
它使用一个现代化的
forward-looking architecture
前瞻性的结构
that has delivered some major
实现了很多重大提升
Our new build system uses
我们的新构建系统
process separation, has a
使用程序隔离  有一个
unified dependency graph, and
统一的依赖性图标
has improved configuration
还有提升的配置分析
And we've used our new
我们还使用了新结构
architecture to improve
去增强并联和缓存
parallelism and caching to
以此来缩短
reduce overall build times.
整体构建时间
I'd like to dig into this for a
我想深入讲解一下
The build process involves two
构建过程包括
main pieces.
两大块
There's the build system that
也就是负责管理和协调
manages and coordinates tasks
任务的构建系统
and the build tools like
以及构建工具
compilers and linkers.
比如 compiler 和 linker
Together, these make up the
两者一起构成了
total build time.
整体构建时间
Now, the work for these
这些部分的工作量
components grows with the size
随着你项目规模的扩大
of your project.
而增加
The larger the project, the more
项目越大  每个部分的
work there is for each
工作量也就越大
Now, this view represents a full
这个视图代表了整体构建
But most of the time, we are
但在大多数时候
incrementally building our
我们要循序渐进地构建项目
projects, only changing a few
每次只改变一小部分
files at a time.
文件
While there is a less work in
这时  构建工具的
these cases for the build tools,
工作量就很小
for larger projects, there are
对于大型项目来说
still a number of details to
还有很多细节要
manage.
管理
This is an area we've focused on
这是我们在 Xcode 9 中集中发力的
with Xcode 9.
一个环节
In our new build system, we've
在我们的新构建系统中
made the build operations
我们让构建操作
two-and-a-half times faster than
比以前快了
they were before.
2.5 倍
And if you add on top of this --
如果你再加上
yep, it's fast [laughter] -- and
是的  它很快[笑声]
if you add on top of this the
如果你再加上刚才说到的
40% improvement we've seen in
混合搭配项目的编程
compilation with mix-and-match
过程中提升的 40%
projects, then you can see a
那么你就会看到
marked improvement with Xcode 9
在构建中使用 Xcode 9
in the build, new build system
新的构建系统比
compared to the previous
原来的版本的提升
release.
是非常大的
Now, the new build system is
新构建系统
designed to be compatible with
设计时就考虑到要和你们的项目
your projects, and we've made a
兼容  在 Xcode 9 里
preview available in Xcode 9.
有一个预览
You can opt in in the Workspace
你可以在工作空间设置
Settings to try it out, and
中选择尝试它
we'll be making it the default
很快我们就会把它设成
build system coming soon.
默认构建系统了
Now, another core technology
另外一项我们大力投入的核心技术
area we've invested in is source
就是源码控制
control, and I'm curious.
我很好奇
A show of hands.
请举一下手
How many of you have GitHub
有多少人有 GitHub
accounts?
账户
All right.
好的
Craig raised his hand.
Craig 举手了
So you are in great company
你们绝不是一个人
because our good friends at
因为我们在 GitHub 的好朋友
GitHub let us know that on the
告诉我们  在桌面上
desktop, two-thirds of all pull
三分之二的 pull request
request related activities
相关的行为都
happen from a Mac.
来自于 Mac
So we thought we could do
因此我们认为这里
something special here, which is
可以下些功夫
why we have integrated
因此我们把
GitHub.com and GitHub Enterprise
GitHub.com 和 GitHub Enterprise
with Xcode 9.
集成到了 Xcode 9 里
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
After you add your GitHub
在你添加 GitHub 账户后
account, you can use Xcode's new
你可以使用 Xcode 的新
cloning work flow that presents
Clone 工作流了  它展示了
all of your projects and search
你在 GitHub 上的所有项目
results from GitHub.
和搜索结果
You can add stars, review
你可以添加星标
project details, even check out
查看项目细节
ReadMe's before you access the
甚至在访问项目之前就查看 Readme
project.
文件
Once you clone a project, you
一旦你 clone 了一个项目
can use Xcode's new source
你就能用 Xcode 的新
control navigator, and this
源码控制导航
presents all of your working
这展示了你的所有
copies, including details like
副本  包括分支
branches, tags, remotes, even
标签 remote
push and pull counts.
push 和 pull count 这些细节
And this is just the start of
这只是我们为你准备的
some of the amazing new source
一系列特别出色的新
control work flows we have for
源码控制工作流的一个开始
And to show you more, I'd like
更多内容 我要请上
to bring up Mike Ferris to give
Mike Ferris 来为大家
you a demonstration.
做一个展示
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Hi. Thanks, Matthew.
&gt;&gt;  嗨  谢谢 Matthew
Hello. I'm going to show you
大家好  我今天要展示一些
today some of the great new ways
在 Xcode 里使用源码控制的
to work with source control in
一些很棒的新方式
Let's get started with GitHub.
咱们就从 GitHub 开始吧
I'm already c1nnected, and here
我已经连上了
in the new clone window, all of
这个新的 clone 窗口
my GitHub repositories are front
我的 GitHub 库就在中间
Today, I actually want to find
现在我想要找到
the Swift Foundation Project, so
Swift Foundation Project
I'm going to search GitHub.
所以我在 GitHub 上搜索
Great. There it is.
好的  找到了
Let's go ahead and clone it.
咱们把它 clone 一下
Once the clone completes, Xcode
一旦 clone 完成
opens the project.
我们就打开项目
Now, my friend Felipe has been
我的朋友 Felipe 总说
telling me about some recent
数据类最近有了些
changes to the data class, and I
新变化  我去
wanted to take a look.
看一看
The new source control navigator
新的源码控制导航
allows me to explore a project.
允许我浏览项目
I can select the current branch
我可以选择当前分支
to show its history, and I see
显示它的历史  我看到
all of the commits, including
所有的提交记录
avatars for the commit authors
包括提交者的头像
and annotations for things like
和标签等注释内容
I can filter commits by author
我可以根据提交者或是提交信息
or commit message, so I'll start
筛选提交记录
by finding Felipe's commits, and
我先找 Felipe 的提交
then I'll narrow it down a
然后在进一步缩小范围
little bit more to just the
只看关于 Beta
commits that have to do with
的提交记录
This is the one that I was
这就是我在找的
looking for.
提交记录
When I double-click a commit, I
我双击一个提交记录
go to the new commit viewer
就进入新的提交视图
where I can see the actual
在这里我可以看到
source changes.
真实的代码变化
It's really easy to browse
浏览历史非常容易
history and to find specific
查找特定的提交记录也不难
Now, I can also seamlessly use
现在  我还可以在改动的同时
source control while I'm making
无缝使用源码控制
changes, and I have another
我还有另一个需要
project that needs a little work
稍作修改的项目
that I'll open now.
现在我把它打开
Before I get started, I want to
在开始前  我要做一个
make a branch.
分支
In the new source control
在新的源码控制导航中
navigator, I'll use the Context
我要使用 Context 菜单
menu to make a new branch for
制作一个分支  名字叫
"master."
"master"
And, OK. I'm all checked out on
好的  新的分支弄好了
my new branch, and I'm ready to
我可以开始了
In my projects, I like the
在我的项目里  我想让
groups to match up with the
群组与文件夹相匹配
folders, and this project is
这个项目已经这样
already set up that way.
设定好了
But it's been bugging me that
但让我不爽的是
these two camera model classes
这两个相机模型类
are in the wrong group.
在错误的群组里
It's OK, though, because now
不过这不要紧
when I move these files to the
因为现在我把这些文件
correct group, Xcode finally
移动到正确的群组后
also moves them to the correct
Xcode 就会自动把它们移动到正确的
folder.
文件夹了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So in projects where the group
在群组和文件夹的层级
and folder layout are the same,
是一样的项目里面
Xcode will now keep them the
Xcode 会让它们保持一致
And when I commit, all the
我提交时  所有的更改
changes will be recorded, so
都会被记录  因此
I'll go ahead and commit this
我会继续提交
now, and I think I'm ready to
我想我已经准备好
land this branch.
完成这个分支了
Back in the source control
回到源码控制导航上面
navigator, I'll select the
我会选择
destination branch and again use
目的分支  并再次使用
the Context menu to merge in the
Context 菜单融入
changes for my working branch.
我的工作分支的更改
And that's it.
这就完成了
I can see that my new commit is
我看到我的新提交
now on the master branch, and I
已经在主分支上了
think I'm ready for my first
我想我准备好首个
beta release.
beta  发布了
So I should probably make a tag.
因此我也许应该做一个标签
I can use the Context menu here
我可以在这里用 Context 菜单
to make a tag from any commit.
为任何提交做标签
OK, I think I'm ready to share
好了  我想我可以分享它了
Now, this project isn't on
现在  这个项目还没有到
GitHub yet, but I can easily put
GitHub 上面  但我可以很容易
it there.
把它放上去
I'll just choose to create a new
我只需选择  生成一个
GitHub remote.
GitHub remote
All these defaults look pretty
所有默认看上去都不错
good, so let's go.
可以开始了
Xcode is now creating a project
Xcode 现在正在 GitHub 上面
on GitHub and pushing up my
生成一个项目
repository with its entire
并把我的库及其完整历史推上去
And now, my project is hosted on
现在  我的项目已经在
GitHub.
GitHub 上了
I have a new origin remote.
我有一个新的源 remote 了
And from there, I can jump
我可以从这里直接跳到
directly to the Project page on
GitHub.com 的
GitHub.com.
项目页面上
Here it is.
完成了
Now, we've worked really closely
我们和 GitHub 的朋友们
with the GitHub folks on all
在这个集成上面并肩奋斗
this integration, and GitHub.com
GitHub.com 也有一个
has a great new feature as well.
非常棒的新特性
Xcode users can now directly
Xcode 用户现在可以直接
clone and open in Xcode using
使用这个新的 Open in Xcode 按钮
this new Open in Xcode button.
在 Xcode 里面 clone 并打开了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Yeah. And that is Source Control
这就是 Xcode 9 里的源码控制
and GitHub in Xcode 9.
和 GitHub 内容
Matthew?
Matthew
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Mike.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Mike
Xcode 9 also includes some
Xcode 9 还包括很多
advancements in our debugging
在 debug 和 runtime 分析工具
and runtime analysis tools.
上的更新
I'd like to start with the view
我想先讲视图 debug 工具
View controllers play an
视图控制器在 UI 开发中
important role in UI
的角色非常重要
development, so we're going to
所以我们要
incorporate them into the view
把它包含到视图 debug
debugging experience.
体验中去
Captures will now include view
Captures 现在会在层级中
controllers in the hierarchy and
包含视图控制
draw them on the canvas above
并在它们管理的视图之上
the views they manage.
把它描绘出来
Together, these will help you
这会帮助你导航
navigate and give you a sense of
并帮助你理解
your view controller boundaries.
你的视图控制边界
The view debugger will now also
视图 debug 工具
include details from SpriteKit
还会包括 SpriteKit 场景的细节
scenes, and the view debugger is
视图 debug 工具是
a perfect way to expand and
扩展并反转你的场景
rotate your scenes, scope
范围  甚至查看裁剪区域
ranges, even look at clipped
的完美方式
We'll also include support for
我们还包含了对
SceneKit scenes as well.
SceneKit 场景的支持
And here you can use the
你可以用熟悉的
familiar SceneKit editor to
SceneKit 编辑器去
rotate the camera, navigate, and
反转相机  导航
inspect objects.
检查对象
So view controller's SpriteKit
视图控制器的 SpriteKit
and SceneKit are now great
和 SceneKit 现在都
additions to our visual
被加入了视觉 debug 工作中
debugging.
这很棒
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Over the last few years, we've
在过去几年中
added runtime sanitizers to our
我们加入了 runtime 清理工具
debugging experience, and they
在 debug 体验中
have been wildly successful at
它们在帮助找出错误这方面
helping track down issues.
获得了很大成功
In addition to advancements in
除了两个已有的清理工具
our two existing sanitizers,
的改进之外
this year, we're adding two new
今年  我们又加入了两个
runtime analysis tools, the
runtime 分析工具
Undefined Behavior Sanitizer and
Undefined Behavior Sanitizer 和
the Main Thread API Checker.
Main Thread API Checker
Programming languages have some
编程语言有一些
undefined behaviors, such as
未定义行为  比如
what to do with misaligned
如何处理偏离的指针
pointers or when encountering
以及遇到带符号整数
signed integer overflows.
溢出时该怎么办
When these situations occur,
在这些情况出现时
they are very difficult to
会非常难以
debug.
debug
The Undefined Behavior Sanitizer
Undefined Behavior Sanitizer
catches many of these cases and
能够抓取很多类似情景
displays details to help you
并显示细节  以帮助你
investigate.
调查
Now, the Main Thread API Checker
你们一定会爱上
is one you're all going to love.
Main Thread API Checker
Calling UI-related APIs from a
从后台线程调用 UI 相关的 API
background thread is a common
这是一个常见错误
mistake and can lead to visual
可能会导致视觉缺陷
defects and random crashes.
和随机崩溃的情况
The Main Thread API Checker
Main Thread API Checker
catches AppKit and UIKit APIs
能够捕捉到未被主线程调用的
not called from the main thread
AppKit 和 UIKit API
and then surfaces issues for you
然后显示错误  帮助你
to investigate.
调查
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
We love this one so much that
我们超爱这一点  于是
we've enabled it by default.
把它设成默认启动了
So when you start debugging with
所以在你开始用 Xcode 9
Xcode 9, you're going to get
debug 时  会自动获取
this behavior for free.
这一行为
Now, our two new runtime
我们两个新的 runtime
sanitizers are available in the
清理器在你的计划的
Diagnostic Options of your
Diagnostic Options 中可以找到
scheme, and all of our
所有的诊断工具
diagnostic tools are available
都可以在运行和测试设置中
for the Run and Test actions,
找到
making them perfect for use with
这让它们可以很完美地契合
continuous integration, which is
持续集成使用
also a perfect segue into our
这就引出了我们的
next section.
下一个部分
We believe that continuous
我们相信  持续集成
integration is an essential
是开发伟大软件的
piece of developing great
重要关键
software, so we're making it
让我们
easier to use Xcode Server by
使用 Xcode Server 变得更容易
including all of the
我们把所有的功能
functionality in Xcode itself.
都放在了 Xcode 里面
You no longer need to install
你们不再需要安装
the macOS Server app.
macOS 服务器 app 了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
A new, simplified UI in the
在 Preferences 中
Preferences takes just a few
一个新的  简化的 UI
clicks to get started, and we've
只需点击几下就能开始
integrated new provisioning work
我们还集成了预备工作流
flows, including automatic and
包括自动和手动
manual code signing to
代码签字
streamline your configuration.
让你的配置加速
Now, on the testing side, a
在测试方面
popular request we've integrated
我们集成了一个流行的请求
is support for testing multiple
就是支持测试多个
applications.
app
Your UI tests can now branch out
你们的 UI 测试现在可以
into many other apps, which is a
分支到很多其他 app 上去
great improvement for working
这对 app 扩展  设置
with app extensions, settings,
和其他的集成工作流来说
and other integrated work flows.
是很好的改进
Additionally, you'll find that
此外  你们还会发现
we've focused on performance for
我们还加强了
UI testing as well.
UI 测试的性能
UI testing queries run three
UI 测试询问
times faster than they did
的运行速度比以前快3倍
And if you adopt new query APIs,
如果你采用了新的询问 API
your own tests can run up to ten
那么你自己的测试速度
times faster than before.
将比以前快 10 倍
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
But we didn't stop there because
但我们不止如此
you'll also find testing with
你还会发现使用
xcodebuild now defaults to
xcodebuild 测试  现在已经默认
running in parallel for multiple
在多个目的之间同时
destinations.
运行了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
This means your command-line
这意味着你的命令行
testing and your Xcode Server
测试和你的 Xcode Server bot
bots can evaluate tests on many
可以在不同设备
devices and simulators all at
和模拟器上同时
the same time.
评估测试了
And speaking of the simulator,
说到模拟器
the simulator app now supports
模拟器 app 现在支持用同一个 app
multiple booted devices for iOS,
使用 iOS  tvOS  watch OS 等
tvOS, and watchOS all in one
多个启动的设备了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Multiple simulator sessions is a
多模拟器会话
huge productivity win when
在测试不同配置
testing different configurations
以及评估多客户场景时
and when evaluating multi-client
意味着生产力的重大提高
You'll also find the simulator
你还会发现模拟器
has a new experience.
有了一个新体验
We've added in a bezel around
我们在边缘加入了
the side to give you familiar
边框  给你控制硬件的熟悉感
access to hardware controls and
并且启动了交互
enable interactivity, such as
比如从边缘进行
swipe gestures from the edge.
扫动手势等
And we've also made the
我们还让模拟器
simulator fully resizable.
的大小可以调整
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So there's one more feature in
还有一个 Xcode 9 的特性
Xcode 9 that I'd like to share
是我想要和你们分享的
with you, and it starts by
它始于我们
something that we're taking
一直想取消的一样东西
away, and it's the need to use
不如直接减少对
one of these.
这个东西的需求
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
You know, I was going to say, I
我本想说
know you all love your USB
我知道你们都爱
cables, but that's apparently
USB 线  但那显然
not true [laughter].
是假话 [笑声]
But it doesn't matter because in
但那不重要
Xcode 9, it's no longer
因为在 Xcode 9 里  不再需要它了
We are adding in wireless
我们加入了无线开发功能
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
With Xcode 9, you can use the
在 Xcode 9 里  你可以用
connection type best suited for
最适合你需要的连接方式
your needs -- USB, Wi-Fi, or
USB WiFi  或者以太网
Ethernet -- when connecting to
连接到你的
your iOS and tvOS devices.
iOS 或者 tvOS 设备上
All of the development work
所有的开发工作流
flows are supported with
都会得到
wireless development.
无线开发的支持
In fact, you can also use
实际上  你可以把
wireless development with other
无线开发用在其他 app 上
apps, like Accessibility
比如 Accessibility
Inspector, QuickTime Player, and
Inspector QuickTime Player 还有
Console.
Console
So this will be a natural
这会很自然地
addition to your development
添加到你的开发
work flows.
工作流中去
So that's just a taste of what
这就是我们在 Xcode 9 里
we have for you in Xcode 9 -- a
为你准备的一些东西
new Source Editor with
新的重构的源码编辑器
refactoring alongside Swift 4; a
和 Swift 4
new indexer, build system, and
新的索引  构建系统
source control work flows
集成了 GitHub 的
integrating GitHub; and
源码控制工作流
advancements in our debugging,
还有 debug 分析和测试工具
analysis, and testing tools to
的增强
go alongside wireless
以及无线开发
All that and more is in Xcode 9,
一切全在 Xcode 9 里
and that's our tools update for
还有更多  这就是今天讲的工具更新
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Next, we'd like to share with
接下来  我们想和你分享
you some of the new APIs we have
一些我们为你准备的新 API
for you, and for that, I'm going
我想请 Josh Shaffer 上台
to invite up Josh Shaffer.
为大家讲解
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Matthew.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Matthew
I'm really excited to tell you
我很兴奋  要告诉大家
about so many of the new and
iOS 11 里很多很多
enhanced APIs in iOS 11.
新的和增强的 API
There's a ton of new things, so
新东西太多了
let's start with the most
咱们就从最重要的
important new API, drag and
API 讲起吧  那就是  拖拽与放置
Drag and drop is simple to use,
拖拽与放置  简单易用
with consistent interactions
在系统中持续交互
across the system, and of
当然  还很容易
course, it's also really easy to
就能够添加到
add to your apps as well.
你们的 app 里
While simple, it's also
不但简单  还非常灵活
incredibly flexible and
而且可以自定义
customizable, and it takes full
全面利用了
advantage of iPad's multi-touch
iPad 的多点触碰
capabilities.
功能
And of course, it's secure by
当然  设计上是安全的
design, allowing access to the
被拖拽的数据
data being dragged only once a
只有在被放置之后
drop occurs.
才能被访问
Adding drag and drop to your
把拖拽放置添加到
apps is almost as easy as using
app 里面  几乎和使用它一样容易
It's completely automatic for
对于标准的文本和网络控制来说
standard text and web controls,
它是完全自动的
so your apps may actually
因此你们的 app 其实没准
already support it.
早已经支持它了
Existing apps like Slack can
现有的 app 比如 Slack
already participate -- for
就是这样
example, by accepting drops of
比如  它可以接受
text in their existing text
把文本拖拽到现有的文本视图上去
views.
在其他情况下  你还需要
do a little work.
做一点小工作
Now, if you're displaying your
如果你在表格视图
content in a table view or a
或者集合视图上
collection view, new delegate
显示内容
methods make it really easy to
新的委托方法会让
add drag-and-drop support with
添加拖拽放置变得异常简单
just a few lines of code.
只需几行代码就可以
Beginning a drag is as easy as
开始拖拽  就像
providing the data, and
提供数据那样容易
accepting a drop is just as
接受放置也一样简单
For everything else, there's an
对于其他一切东西
easy-to-use, standard API that
这个简单易用的标准 API
can integrate with all of your
可以整合到你们所有的
custom views.
自定义视图上
By default, the API provides
这个 API 默认提供
standard gestures and
标准手势和动画
animations, but it's fully
但它也是完全可以自定义的
You can customize the lift
你可以自定义
animations that occur at the
在拖拽开始时的
start of a drag, add multiple
抬升动画
items to an already in-progress
向正在进行的拖拽过程添加多个项目
drag, generate custom preview
为每个项目生成自定义预览图像
images for each item, choose the
选择显示在被拖拽
badge to display on the dragged
项目上的标志
item to indicate that it will be
以表示它将被移动或复制
moved or copied, and even
你甚至可以
provide fully custom set-down
提供完全自定义的
animations to play when the drop
放置动画  供放置时使用
The API is flexible enough that
这个 API 非常灵活
even the really custom,
就算在日历 app 中
gesture-based event creation and
那种高度自定义的
reordering in the Calendars app
基于手势的事件生成与重新安排
was able to be re-implemented on
都可以在拖拽放置 API 之上
top of the drag-and-drop APIs.
进行重新实现
And the flexibility doesn't just
这种灵活性不仅
end with the appearance.
停留在表面
The data model is incredibly
数据模型也同样
flexible as well.
非常灵活
It can work with any type of
可以兼容你 app 使用的
data that your app uses,
任何类型数据
allowing you to support really
允许你支持非常
rich interactions.
丰富的交互
For example, locations dragged
比如  从地图上
out of maps include rich
拖拽出的地点就包括
location information and really
丰富的定位信息
detailed drag previews.
以及富有细节的拖拽预览
Now, with drag and drop, even
现在  有了拖拽与放置
existing interactions get
现有的交互体验也会变得更好
Reminders uses UITableView's
Reminders 使用 UITableView
built-in reordering support to
内置的重新安排支持
allow you to quickly reorder and
允许你快速重排与
organize your tasks.
组织你的任务
You can begin a drag to drag an
你可以开始拖拽  拖拽一个
item, to move it to a different
项目  把它移动到一个不同的位置
spot, and now even pick up
甚至可以拾取
multiple reminders and move them
多个提醒  让它们在
between lists so that you can
列表之间移动  以便你能够
really quickly organize all of
非常快速地组织你的
your tasks.
所有任务
Because all of this is built on
因为所有这些都是在
top of a common API, it works
一个普通 API 的基础上构建的
seamlessly together as well.
因此它们会无缝工作
You can bring out Calendar, and
你可以打开 Calendar
begin dragging one of those
开始拖拽其中一个事件
events, and drag it over into
把它直接拖到
Reminders, where you can drop it
Reminders 里面  把它放置在里面
to quickly add it to your to-do
这样就能快速把它加到任务列表了
list.
拖拽正在进行的过程中
progress, the system handles
系统会响应触摸这个动作
that touch, leaving your app
让你的 app 完全可交互
fully interactive and free to
能够响应
respond to any other touches.
其他的触摸动作
This makes it really easy to
这让需要你的 app
support even complex
内部导航的
interactions that require
复杂交互
navigation within your app, such
变得很简单
as moving photos between albums.
比如在不同相册之间转移照片
Now, on the iPad, the entire OS
在 iPad 上  整个 OS
remains fully interactive,
都完全可交互
allowing you to pick up multiple
允许你在一个地方拾取
items in one place and then
多个项目
navigate freely around the
并在系统中自由导航
system, even switching apps,
甚至切换 app
bringing those dragged items
同时携带这些被拖拽的项目
with you so that you can use
以便把它们应用在
them somewhere else.
其他地方
During all this navigation, the
在整个导航过程中
data behind the drag is being
拖拽背后的数据
protected from unintended access
受到保护
by any other apps that you're
不会受到其拖拽路径上的其他 app 的
dragging it over.
无意访问
Until a drag is completed, only
在拖拽完成之前
metadata is made available to
潜在放置目的对象
potential drop destinations.
是可以访问元数据的
When a drop does occur, the data
放置的时候
is quickly made available to the
数据就很快能被
receiving app.
接收 app 访问了
Now, the security provided by
这个 lazy delivery
this lazy delivery doesn't have
提供的安全性
to come at the cost of
并不是以性能
performance either because even
为代价的  因为
really large files can be
大型文件
transferred almost instantly
也可以几乎在瞬间
with APFS cloning.
使用 APFS cloning 传送
Now, this is all just the
这一切不过
beginning.
是开始
To show you some other exciting
接下来要向大家展示
use cases and to give you an
另外一些令人振奋的案例
idea of how easy it can be to
并展示向你的 app
add drag and drop to your apps
添加拖拽放置有多么容易
as well, Eliza Block will now
有请 Eliza Block
come up and give us a demo.
上台为大家演示
Eliza?
Eliza
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Josh.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Josh
So I'd like to begin by showing
我想先展示一下
an improvement that we've made
我们对 iOS 主屏幕的改进
to the iOS Home screen by
这是通过
leveraging the drag-and-drop
拖拽放置 API 实现的
So here on this iPad, I can
在这个 iPad 上
press and hold to begin
我可以通过长按 home 键来
reordering my apps.
重新安排我的 app
For example, I could create, I
比如 我可以创建
could drag reminders over the
我可以把 reiminder 拖拽到
Calendar to create a
Calendar 上面  创建一个
Productivity folder.
效率文件夹
Now, in iOS 11, we have
现在  在 iOS 11 里
completely rewritten app
我们使用拖拽放置
reordering using drag and drop,
完全重写了重新归置 app 的功能
and we've made it a whole lot
我们让它变得
more powerful.
更加强大了
Let's find some more
我们再找一些
productivity apps to add to this
效率 app 加到这个文件夹里
Here's Pages.
这个是 Pages
I'll begin dragging it, and as I
我开始拖拽它
do, the Home screen remains
我这样做的时候  主屏幕
fully interactive, so with my
仍然是完全可交互的
other hand, I can swipe between
用我的另一只手  我可以
pages, navigate in and out of
在不同页面上扫动
folders, and the best part is
进出文件夹  最棒的是
I'm no longer limited to
我不再受限于
dragging a single app at a time.
每次只能拖拽一个 app 了
I can tap Keynote to add it to
我可以点击 Keynote 把它
my ongoing drag, close the
加入到我正在进行的拖拽中
folder, and let's look around
关闭文件夹  我们看一看
and see if we can find Numbers.
能不能找到 Numbers
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
There it is, so I'll tap it,
找到了  我点一下
grab it, and now I can drag all
抓住它  现在我可以
three of these apps back over to
把这三个 app  拖拽回
the first page and drop them
第一页  然后只要一下
into my folder in one fell
就能把它们全部放到文件夹里
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So that's app reordering with
这就是使用拖拽放置
drag and drop, and you can do
重新归置 app 的方法
this kind of thing in your own
你可以在你自己的 app 中
applications too.
也做到类似的事
To see an example, let me launch
来看一个例子
this app called Byte Swap that
我要打开这个叫做 Byte Swap 的 app
my team has written to help me
这是我的团队写的 app
view and organize my Swift
它能帮我浏览和组织我的
Playgrounds trading cards.
Swift Playgrounds 交换卡
So it's composed of a Swift,
它有一个 Swift
sorry, a split-view controller,
不好意思  是有一个分割视图控制器
and on the right here, you can
在屏幕右边  你可以
see that my cards are displayed
看到我的卡片
in a collection view using a
通过基本浮动布局
basic flow layout.
以集合视图呈现
Now, I think it would be cool if
现在我想
I could pick up these cards and
如果我能拾取这些卡片
drag them around to reorder
使用拖拽来重新归置它们
them, move them between my
让它们在不同相册中移动
different albums, and so let's
这一定会很酷
actually go ahead and implement
所以咱们现在就开始
that now.
这样做吧
I'll switch over to Xcode, where
我要切换到 Xcode
I have the Cards View controller
我已经打开了卡片视图控制器
Now, because Table View and
因为 Table View 和
Collection View already contain
Collection View 已经包含了
built-in support for drag and
对拖拽与放置的内置支持
drop, adding drag and drop if
所以如果你正在使用
you're using one of these
这些类  那么添加拖拽放置功能
classes is really simple.
就真的很简单了
I'll start by just declaring
首先我只需
conformance to the new
声明遵守新的
UICollectionView drag/delegate
UICollectionView 拖拽／委托协议
protocol.
我这样做时 Xcode 就会
informs me that I have not yet
通知我  我还没有履行协议
implemented one of the required
要求必须使用的某个方法
methods in that protocol, and I
我可以点击这个错误
can tap the issue and accept the
接受 Fix-it
Fix-it to add the protocol
来添加协议
So this method, Items for
因此  这个方法
Beginning Session, is prompting
Items for Beginning Session
me to package up the data for
提示我要将被拖拽的
the item being dragged, and I'm
项目数据打包
going to do that by calling out
因此我要调出一个
to a helper method that I wrote
我之前写的帮助方法
before, which just packages up
它会把数据打包成
the data as an image and makes
一个图像  并让它可拖拽
That's actually all I have to do
我为了让拖拽的基本框架
to get the bare bones of drag
在这个 app 内生效
working in this application, but
其实  要做的事已经做完了
I also want to make it possible
但我还想通过点击来向
to tap to add items to an
正在进行的拖拽
ongoing drag.
添加项目
So I'm going to add a second
所以我要再添加
method to do that, and then
一个方法  然后
we'll go ahead and run this.
我们可以做这个
I'll switch over to my iPad.
我切换到 iPad 上
Whoops. And here it is.
好了  出现了
As you can see, now I can pick
你们可以看到
this guy up and drag him around.
我现在可以把这个家伙捡起来到处拖拽
But I can't reorder yet because
但我还不能重新安排位置
I haven't implemented drop in
因为我还没有在这个 app 中
this application.
实现放置
However, I still can freely
不过我仍然可以
interact with the app and I can
在 app 中自由互动
pick up a second item to add it
并拾取第二个项目
to my existing drag, and this is
添加到正在进行的拖拽中
actually more useful than it
实际上这比看上去更加实用
looks because, in addition to
因为我不但能够
being able to drag these
把这些东西拖拽到各处
arounds, I can interact with
我还可以与其他
other apps which may have
可能已经实现了放置的 app
implemented drop already.
进行交互
For example, Mail.
比如 Mail
So I can go into Mail, tap to
我可以打开 Mail
compose a message, and then drop
点击写邮件  然后
these two cards in the message
把这两张卡片放进去
just like that.
就这样
So that's with only two delegate
只需要把两个委托方法
methods added to my existing
添加到现有的 app 中去
All right, switching back over
好了  切换回 Xcode
to Xcode, let's go ahead and
让我们继续
implement drop.
实现放置
So I will start once again by
我再次声明
declaring conformance to a new
遵守新的委托协议
delegate protocol,
也就是 UICollectionView 放置委托
And Xcode will once again offer
Xcode 会再次
to fill in the missing protocol
提示我完成缺失的协议步骤
So this perform drop method is a
这个执行放置方法
little bit more involved.
会稍微复杂一点
I have to update my model for
我必须要更新我的模型
the, to, by receiving the new
让它接受新的
drop data, and, also, I'm
放置数据
customizing the animation here a
我也在这里使用帮助方法
little bit with a helper method.
自定义了动画
And there's one other method I
我还要再添加
need to add as well, which is
一个方法
called as I drag my finger over
我把手指拖过
one of the drop targets, and it,
一个放置目标时会调用它
that's what causes the
它会让集合视图
Collection View to open up a gap
打开一个缺口
so that I can reorganize within
这样我就能在某个特定列表中
a particular list.
重新组织了
So switching over to my iPad
再次切换回我的 iPad
again, this time when I pick up
这次我再拾取一张卡片
a card, the other ones move out
其他卡片会让出路来
of the way, and I can still
我仍然可以在列表间切换
switch between lists, grab a
拿起更多的卡片
couple more, and then I can drop
然后我可以把它们
them all together in my
一起放置到我最喜欢的
Favorites album.
相册里去
So easy. So that's adding drag
非常简单
and drop to your applications.
这就是在你的 app 中添加拖拽与放置
And switching gears, we've been
我们和不少
working with a number of
伙伴共同工作
partners who have been working
他们一直努力让
on getting drag and drop in
拖拽和放置进入
their applications.
他们的应用
And one partner that has really
其中一个合作伙伴
stood out for their creative use
创造性地使用了这个 API
of this API is Adobe.
那就是 Adobe
So now, I would like to invite
所以现在我想请
up Brooke Francesi from Adobe to
Adobe 的 Brooke Francesi 上台
show you what they've built.
为你展示他们的成果
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Eliza.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Eliza
I cannot wait to show you what
我已经迫不及待地想
drag and drop can mean for the
给你们展示拖拽放置对于
creative professional.
创意行业的意义了
This is Adobe Photoshop Sketch,
这是 Adobe Photoshop Sketch
and it's a focused painting and
它是专用于油画与图画的 app
drawing app with some of the
在它里面  有很多
best natural media brushes,
最好用的 natural media brushes
including all of My Photoshop
包括 My Photoshop Brushes 里的
Brushes.
全部笔刷
I've been working on this
我在画这副插画
illustration, and before I
在完成之前
finish it up, I want to add a
我想在背景中
few elements to the background.
添加一些元素
And in order to do that, I'm
要做到这一点
going to open another Adobe app
我要打开另一个 Adobe app
called Capture.
叫做 Capture
Capture is an app that allows me
Capture 这个 app 允许我
to capture inspiration from the
捕捉周围世界的灵感
world around me to create things
生成图案
like patterns, color themes, and
色彩主题  甚至是自定义笔刷等等
even custom brushes, which I've
我在这个项目中
been using to work on this
一直在使用这些笔刷
Now, in order to add some
现在  为了在背景中
elements to the background, I
添加一些元素
need to load the color theme
我需要把色彩主题
into my toolbar in Photoshop
读取到 Photoshop Sketch 的工具栏里
In the past, I would've had to
在过去  我得去
go find all those colors,
找到所有的色彩
manually load every single one
用手动方式把每一种色彩
of them into my toolbar, go
读取到工具栏里
back, find the brushes.
然后再回去  找到笔刷
You get it.
你懂的
It's a pretty long and arduous
那是一个很长又很麻烦的
process.
过程
But with drag and drop, I can
但使用拖拽放置
select all five colors at once,
我可以一下选择五种色彩
navigate to my Brushes tab,
导航到我的笔刷中
select the two brushes that I've
选择我在这个项目中用到的
been using to work on in this
两种笔刷
project, and simultaneously drag
然后同时把它们
them over into my toolbar.
拖拽到我的工具栏里
Pretty awesome, right?
真够厉害  是不是
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Something that would've taken me
这在之前要花上
a ton of steps before took me
很多步骤才能完成  现在却只要
just seconds.
几秒钟
We even took advantage of the
我们甚至还利用这个
API to create our own custom
API 去生成我们自己的自定义
animations.
动画
Once we got our hands on the new
我们开始使用新的
drag and drop, we were amazed at
拖拽放置后  惊讶不已
how simple and straightforward
它的实现竟是如此
it was to implement.
简单直接
Within just two days, we had one
只用了两天时间
engineer who had the basic API
我们的一个工程师就让
feature working in one app, and
基本的 API 特性在一个 app 里实现了
so we just decided to keep
于是我们决定继续挖掘
The possibilities with drag and
拖拽放置带来的可能性
drop are literally endless.
真的是无穷无尽的
The cool thing is is I'm not
最酷的是这不仅
limited to just images, and
限于图像  笔刷
brushes, and color themes.
以及色彩主题
I can actually drag and drop
我还能在不同的 app 之间
layers between multiple apps.
拖拽放置图层
Now, I want to see what this is
现在  我想看看它在 Context
going to look like in Context.
里的效果怎么样
Actually, let me draw a little
让我先画上几笔
I want to see what this is going
我想看看在 Context 里
to look like in Context, and so
效果怎样
I'm going to take these layers
我选择这些
that I've been working on by
我之前画的图层
selecting them, I'm going to
打开我的 Dock
open up my Dock, and I'm going
然后把它们都
to drag them into another Adobe
拖拽到另一个 Adobe app 里
app, Photoshop Mix, which is an
这是 Photoshop Mix
image compositing tool.
它是一个图像合成工具
Now, what's really cool is once
在我进来之后
I'm in here, I have options.
我还能有所选择
I can target any specific
我可以在我的画布上
coordinates on my canvas if I
对准任何坐标
know exactly where I want those
如果我确切知道
layers to be, or I can just drag
要把图层放在哪的话
them right into my layer stack.
或者我可以把它们直接放在图层栏里
That's pretty awesome, right?
超棒的  对不对
I never get tired of seeing that
我真是永远都看不够
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Now, in case you've all been
现在 我要总结一下了
asleep for the past two minutes,
怕是有人已经在这两分钟睡过去了
I just dragged three completely
我刚刚从三个
different types of assets
完全不同的 app 中
between three completely
拖拽了三种
different applications.
完全不同的东西
And that's why drag and drop
因此  拖拽与放置
isn't just saving steps in my
绝不仅仅是在我的工作中节省了步骤
It's an entirely new mobile work
它是一个为在 iPad 上
flow for creative professionals
进行创意工作的人准备的
on the iPad.
全新的工作流
Thank you.
谢谢大家
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Brooke.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Brooke
Drag and drop is a really
拖拽放置真是一个令人振奋的
exciting, new API, and we can't
新 API 我们已经迫不及待
wait to see what you're all
要看看你们会用它
going to do with it, but there
做什么 但还有很多
are a number of other
iOS 11 上的其他改进
enhancements in iOS 11 that you
你们也应该
should be aware of as well.
去了解它们
So let's start with some updates
我们说一说
to the user interface.
对用户交互的更新吧
The top level of most
大多数 app 的顶端层级
applications now features a
现在有了一个大标题
large title featured prominently
在导航栏中非常显眼
in the navigation bar, along
还有一项新的
with a new integrated search
集成的搜索栏的
field design.
设计
You'll find this at the top of
在大多数 app 的
most applications, including
顶层  你们会发现它  包括
Messages, Mail, the new App
全新的 Messages Mail  App
Store, Photos, and many more.
Store 和 Photos 等等
And enabling this appearance in
要在你自己的 app 中
your own apps couldn't be any
显示大标题  也是非常简单的
With just a few properties, you
只要调用一些属性
can adopt and control the
你们就能采用并且控制
appearance of the new large
新的外观采用大标题
title and adopt the new
并且采用新的
integrated search field.
搜索框了
You'll also find that in iOS 11,
你们还会发现  在 iOS 11 里
UITableView has now enabled
UITableView 现在已经默认启用
self-sizing cells by default,
自适应尺寸的单元格
helping to make it even easier
这会让你
for you to have great support
更加容易地得到
for dynamic type.
动态字体效果
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
This has also helped to make iOS
这也让 iOS 11 的 UI
11's UI more responsive to text
对于字体变化的响应
size changes than ever before.
比以前更灵活了
And with a wide range of dynamic
有了更广的
type sizes available, your users
动态字体尺寸范围
are going to choose the size
你们的用户就能选择
that's most comfortable for
他们用起来最舒服的字体大小了
Dynamic type is a really
动态字体是一个
commonly used user preference,
使用频繁的用户偏好
so you definitely want to make
所以你们一定要确定
sure that you test with it and
去测试它
respond to it well.
并对它的响应及时
And don't forget to design for
别忘了去为每个人设计
Tests with a larger
使用更大的
accessibility size is enabled as
辅助尺寸进行测试
well because in these instances,
也可行了  在这种情况下
your table view rows will get
你们的表格视图行高会
even taller, so you'll want to
增加
make sure that your content lays
所以你们要确定内容
out well and remains legible,
布局良好  保持易读性
even at those really large
即便是字体很大时也要这样
Next, let's talk about files.
接下来我们说说文件
File management has been
文件管理在 iOS 11 里
completely revamped in iOS 11.
彻底更新了
Now, of course, you can access
当然  你可以在新的
files from the new Files app
Flies app 里访问文件
that you heard about this
你们今天早晨已经听过了
morning, but, even better, a new
但更好的是
document browser with all of the
具有同样功能的
same capabilities can be brought
新的文档浏览器
up and displayed right within
可以在你们的 app 内部
your own apps.
出现了
You can filter the types of
你可以筛选出现在
files that will be displayed
浏览器里的文件
within the browser.
类型
Excuse me, add custom actions
不好意思  在导航栏中
right into the navigation bar,
添加自定义动作
and even allow the creation of
甚至是允许在同一个交互页面
new documents right from within
内部直接生成
the same interface.
新文件
And of course, you can also
当然  你还可以
customize its appearance so that
定义它的外观
it best fits in with the rest of
让它更好地融入
your applications.
你的 app
The document browser also offers
文档浏览器还提供了
really quick access to iCloud
快速访问 iCloud Drive 的
Drive's new document sharing
新分享文档支持
support, enabling easy
让 iOS 和 macOS 之间
collaboration across iOS and
的协作变的更加简单
Using NSFileCoordinator, you can
你可以使用 NSFileCoordinator
easily find out about changes to
轻易找到对这些文档的更改
these documents as they occur,
甚至在
even if the changes are made by
其他用户做出这些更改时
another user.
也可以
And on macOS, NSDocument
在 macOS 上 NSDocument
includes built-in support for
包括对在你的 app
file sharing right within your
内部直接分享文件的支持
Finally, let's talk about iOS
最后  我们来说一说
11's new multitasking features,
iOS 11 的新的多任务功能
enabling your apps to
这让你的 app 能够
participate in the new
参与到新的多任务工作流中来
multitasking work flows enabled
这是由新的浮动 Dock
by the new floating Dock,
slide-over apps
slide-over apps, pinned apps,
pinned apps
and the brand-new App Switcher
和全新的 App Switcher 共同构成的
is really straightforward.
它非常简单直接
If you've adopted size classes,
如果你在过去几年中采用了
flexible layouts, and default
size classes 灵活分层
storyboards over the last few
和默认故事板
years, then you're actually
那么你实际上
already done.
已经完成了
iOS 11 builds on top of these
iOS 11 在这些现有技术的基础上
existing technologies to enable
进行构建  从而诞生了
a whole bunch of new work flows.
一大批新的工作流
Now, if you haven't adopted them
如果你还没有采用上面提到的东西
yet, there's never been a better
现在的时机是最好的
time.
这些都只是一个开始
There's a ton of other new and
在iOS 11 里还有很多
enhanced APIs available in iOS
新的和增强的 API
For example, password autofill
比如  密码自动填充
makes it really quick and secure
让你从 iCloud 钥匙串中
to get login credentials out of
获得登录信息
iCloud Keychain and right into
并直接在你的 app 里登录
your apps, which can really
变得更快  更安全
streamline the login flow for
这对你的 app 登录体验来说
your applications.
是一个很大的提升
It's really great [applause].
这非常棒 [ 掌声 ]
Named color assets and vector
现在在你的素材目录里
assets can now be stored in your
可以保存已命名颜色素材
asset catalogs, and
和向量素材
UIFontMetrics make it really
UIFontMetrics 让你自定义的字体
easy even to have your own
加入动态字体
custom fonts participate in
变得更加容易
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
In addition to all of this,
除此之外
there's also some really great
对于各种 Apple 服务的 API
enhancements to APIs for various
也有很多
Apple services, so let's talk
很棒的改进
about just a few, starting with
我们只能谈一点  就从
iMessage.
iMessage 开始吧
With the new app strip in iOS
有了 iOS 11 里的新应用带
11, Messages apps are now more
信息 app 现在更加容易被发现了
discoverable and they're a lot
而且它们也变得
more powerful as well.
更加强大了
Your apps can now render live
你们的 app 现在可以
content in the message bubbles
在交谈中的聊天气泡中
right in line in the
递交 live 内容了
And with the new direct send
使用新的直接发送 API
API, you can remove a common
你可以帮你的用户
point of friction for your
去除一项痛点
users, making it possible to
让发送信息变得非常简单
really easily send messages with
在你的 app 扩展里
just a single tap from right
只需点击一下
within your app extensions.
就可以完成
Next, SiriKit.
接下来是 SiriKit
The list of supported domains
支持的域扩大了
has expanded to include a number
包括了一些新的域
of new domains, including
比如支付账户
payment accounts, lists, notes,
列表  笔记
QR code display, and more.
二维码显示  等等
And if you missed it, earlier
如果你错过了的话
this year, we greatly simplified
今年早些时候  我们极大地简化了
SiriKit development with the
SiriKit 开发
addition of simulator support
添加了 iOS 和 watchOS 上的
for both iOS and watchOS.
模拟器支持
And finally, Apple Music.
最后是 Apple Music
With MusicKit, adding music
使用 MusicKit 在你们的 app 中
playback to your apps has never
添加音乐回放变得前所未有地简单
Your users can now play any of
用户们现在可以直接在 app 内部
the 40 million songs available
播放为 Apple Music
to Apple Music subscribers right
订阅客户准备的全部
from within your apps.
4000 万首歌曲了
This is especially great for
这对于健身 app 来说
fitness apps, now enabling full
更是好消息
access to songs, playlists, and
现在你们不用中断锻炼
radio stations without ever
就能访问歌曲  播放列表
interrupting your workout.
和广播电台了
Now, these are just some of the
这些只不过是
enhancements to the APIs for
对于 Apple 各种服务的
Apple's various services.
API 的一部分加强
Next, to tell us about some of
接下来  给大家讲解
our exciting new photo and
我们超棒的照片和
imaging APIs, Sebastien
图像 API 改进的是 Sebastien
Marineau-Mes will come up to the
Marineau-Mes  欢迎他上场
Seb?
Seb
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Josh.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Josh
Thank you.
谢谢
Really excited to be here.
来这里真激动
I've got a lot to cover today,
我今天要讲的很多
so let me get started.
咱们马上开始
First, let's talk about our new
首先  我们来说一说
photos project extension on
macOS 上的新的照片项目扩展
You're now able to bring
你现在可以把创意性的
creative, project-based features
基于项目的特性
directly to photos.
直接加入照片了
Users can easily discover your
用户可以在 Mac App Store 里
new extension through a Mac App
轻易发现你们的新扩展
Store.
你把它准备好后
up, users can select photos,
用户可以选择照片
memories, or albums and then
回忆  或者相册
choose your extension from the
然后从 Create 菜单
Create menu.
选择扩展
The Photos app [inaudible]
Photos app
extension to not only images,
扩展不仅限于图像
but also the rich context so
还包括丰富的文本
that project creation feels
这会让生成项目
completely natural.
完全自然
Additionally, we allow you to
此外  我们还允许你
persist your own project data.
保留自己的项目数据
Now, your extension runs within
现在  你们的扩展
the Photos application, so it
在 Photos app 内部运行
really feels like a seamless
所以真的是无缝体验
We, of course, designed it to
当然  我们把它设计成
support print products.
支持打印产品
Here's a great example of this.
这有一个好例子
But you could do a lot more with
但你可以用它做得更多
Here's an example of someone
这里  有人在构建一个
that's built a web publishing
网络出版应用
application or even directly
甚至是直接
ordering framed prints from your
从你的最爱照片中
favorite photo.
订购带框打印
So we think our users are really
我们认为用户一定会
going to love the new extensions
爱上你们用这个建立的
that you're going to create with
扩展去拓展
this extending photos.
他们的照片
Next, let's talk about Camera.
接下来是相机
In iOS 11, the camera has a
在 iOS 11 中的更新
lightweight QR detector, and all
相机有一个轻量化的二维码探测器
you need to do is point your
你只需要把相机对准二维码
camera at one.
就可以了
The QR code is automatically
二维码会自动被解码
decoded and will offer to open a
并可以在合适的 app 中
deep link into the appropriate
打开深层链接
There you go.
就像这样
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Now, it's really simple to use
作为开发者
as a developer.
这很容易使用
You simply need to adopt
你只需采用
Universal Links, and we even
通用链接
support common QR formats, such
我们甚至还支持
as location, contacts, and Wi-Fi
位置  通讯录  和 WiFi 网络
networks.
等二维码格式
Next, let's talk about
接下来是
compression and formats.
压缩与格式
We've, we're making really big
今年我们在这方面的改进
advances here this year.
真的非常大
Now, of course, JPEG is
当然  JPEG 是无所不在的
ubiquitous and has served us
而且在过去 25 年中
really well over the last 25
为我们提供了很好的服务
years, but today we know that a
但今天我们知道
number of technologies offer
有一些技术会提供
better compression and
更好的压缩与
flexibility.
灵活性
And similarly for H.264, which
这对 H.264 也一样
is over a decade old.
它也有超过 10 年的历史了
Now, compression's important,
压缩很重要
but we must consider other
但我们也要考虑到
requirements, so let's look at
其他的要求  所以让我们
some of these.
看看这个
So for example, today the line
举例来说  现在
between photos and videos is
照片与视频之间的界限
blurred, and a lot of what we
已经很模糊了
capture is actually a
我们所拍摄的很多东西
combination of both of these
其实是这两种类型素材的
types of assets.
混合产物
We also have new sensors that
我们也有新的传感器
capture much richer images and
它可以捕捉更丰富的图像
display them, displays that
并显示它们
bring them to life.
栩栩如生
And finally, whatever we choose
说到底  无论我们选择什么格式
has to keep pace with
都必须跟上
ever-increasing resolutions.
日益提高的分辨率
And so for the codec, we've
所以  我们选择了
selected HEVC because it meets
HEVC 作为编解码器  因为
all of these requirements.
它符合上述所有要求
It offers up the 2x compression
它能在同等图像质量下
at equivalent image quality, and
提供2倍压缩率
when you add up the billions of
如果你考虑到数以十亿计的
photos and videos, or trillions
照片与视频
I should say, that adds up to a
或者应该说数以兆计
lot of saved space.
那么节省的空间是很惊人的
HEVC is also hardware
HEVC 也从很多
accelerated across many of our
设备上得到了硬件加速
And finally, it supports photos,
而且它还支持照片
videos, 4K and beyond, and a
视频  4K 及更高分辨率
number of new technologies for
支持很多拍摄与显示的
capture and display.
新技术
We've also selected a new image
我们还选择了一个新的
container called HEIF, or, as I
图像格式  名叫 HEIF
like to call it, "heef."
我习惯叫它 heef
You can repeat after me, "heef."
你们可以跟我一起说 heef
HEIF supports the concept of
HEIF 支持
compound assets, so in a single
复合素材的概念
file, you can have one or more
所以在单一文件里
photos or one or more images.
你可以放下一个或是更多的照片或图像
You can have videos.
还可以是视频
You can have auxiliary data such
还可以有辅助数据
as alpha and Depth.
比如 alpha 和景深
It's also highly extensible.
它也是高度可扩展的
It supports rich metadata,
它支持丰富的元数据
animations and sequences, and
动画和序列  还有其他
other media types, such as
媒体类型  比如音频
audio.
最后 HEIF 是 ISO 标准的
standard, which is critical for
这对生态来说
ecosystem adoption.
非常重要
Now, our standard APIs provide
现在  我们的标准 API
direct support for HEVC and
会直接支持 HEVC 和
HEIF.
HEIF
And generally, it's transparent.
总体上来说  它是显而易见的
No opt in is required.
不需要主动做什么
But there may be cases where you
但有时也许你会想
want to explicitly control the
明确控制格式
So for example, if you're trying
比如  如果你正想
to play a high-resolution movie
在没有硬件加速的
on an older device that doesn't
老设备上播放一部
have hardware acceleration, in
高分辨率的影片
this case, we'd provide you an
在这种情况下  我们为你准备了
API that you can use to
一个 API  你可以用它
determine whether a given file
决定某个文件
-- in this case, an HEVC movie
在这个例子中是 HEVC 格式的电影
-- would play well on this
是否能够在这个设备上顺利播放
device.
如果不行
automatically fall back to one
我们能够自动回退到
of the older formats to maintain
老一点的格式
a great user experience.
来保持良好的用户体验
So now, within our ecosystem, we
现在  在我们的生态系统内部
automatically use HEVC and HEIF
我们已经自动使用 HEVC 和 HEIF 格式
as we share between all
在所有兼容的设备上
compatible devices.
分享文件了
But where, when we're unsure
但如果我们不确定
that the recipient can decode
对方能否解码
these new formats, we'll err on
这些新格式  我们就会
the side of compatibility and
以兼容性为先
automatically transcode the JPEG
自动转码成 JPEG 和
and H.264.
H.264 格式
An example of this would be
举个例子
putting photos in an email
把照片放入 email 附件
I'd really encourage you as you
我真的建议大家
adopt these new formats to be
在采用这些新格式
thoughtful about compatibility
把它们放进你的 app 时
as you build this into your
要多考虑一下兼容性
So that concludes compression,
这就是关于压缩的内容
and let me now talk about
接下来让我来说一说
another new topic, Depth.
另一个新主题  景深
Now, we've all see Portrait Mode
我们都看到了 iPhone 7 Plus
on the iPhone 7 Plus, which
上面的人像模式
generates the Depth effect using
它使用双摄像头生成
the two cameras.
景深效果
Here's how we do it.
我们是这样做的
We capture simultaneous images
我们用两个摄像头
from both cameras and we then
同时捕捉图像
use stereoscopy to compute
然后使用立体视法计算景深
Depth.
这和人类的视觉原理是一样的
We store this in what we call
我们把这个储存在
the depth map.
深度图上面
So in Portrait Mode, we take the
在人像模式下  会拍摄照片
photo, the depth map, and then
和深度图  然后
we use this to blur the objects
我们会用它来模糊掉
that are in the background.
背景中的物体
But what's really cool is that
但最酷的是在
in iOS 11, we're now storing the
iOS 11 里  我们把
depth map as part of what we
深度图存储成拍摄的一部分
capture, and we're giving you
而且我们还要让你
and your app access to the photo
和你的 app 能够访问
and the depth map.
照片和深度图
So you can load it up and then
你可以加载它
you can use this to do your own
使用它完成你自己的
creative effects.
创造性效果
And let me show you a couple of
我来给你们展示
examples of this.
几个例子
So I might take this photo and I
我可以拿出这张照片
might decide to turn the
我决定把背景
background into monochrome,
变成单色的
really highlighting the subject.
这样就突出主题
I might apply a more artistic
我需要使用更加艺术化的
effect.
效果
Maybe I'll replace this with
也许我可以把这个替换成
this pumpkin patch with blur
带模糊效果的南瓜田
And you can imagine even more
你们可以想出
creative effects.
更具创意的效果
In fact, these are just
实际上  这些不过是
examples.
一些示例
The possibilities here are
可能性是无穷无尽的
Now, this is Depth for still
这是静态图像的景深
We're also giving you access to
我们还让你们能够使用
a lower-fidelity, real-time
相机 API 访问较低保真度的
Depth stream using the Camera
实时 Depths 流
APIs.
这让你能够构建
Camera-based applications that
基于相机的应用
will use Depth in a novel way.
让它们以新奇的方式使用 Depths
So Depth is really a simple
Depths 是对于我们的静态图像
extension to both our still
和相机捕捉 API 的
image and Camera capture APIs,
一个简单的扩展
and we look forward to
我们期待着见到
everything that you're going to
你们在这些新 API 之上
be building on top of these new
构建出的东西
APIs.
非常非常期待
Next -- yeah.
接下来  对
There you go.
就是这样
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Next, let's talk about our new
接下来  我们来说说新的
Vision APIs.
影像 API
Now, of course, computer vision
当然  计算机影像
and machine learning already
和机器学习早已
underpin many of the features in
成为了许多 Apple 产品
Apple's products.
特性的基础
You saw that this morning.
你们今天上午已经了解过了
You've also seen apps in the
也在 Store 里见过
Store that use computer vision.
使用计算机影像的 app 了
One of them is the hot dog
其中一个是热狗探测器 app
detection app that was featured
HBO 的剧集《硅谷》
in HBO's Silicon Valley.
里面提到过它
But of course, these apps have
但当然  这些 app
all had to roll computer vision,
全都使用计算机影像
the computer vision technology
把计算机影像
on their own.
用在自己身上
And what we're doing this year
我们今年要做的
is bring all of our great
是让我们所有的
built-in capabilities and making
内置功能都能够
them available to all of you.
为你们所用
So things you can do -- face and
你们可以做的有
landmark detection.
面部特征点检测
We've seen the rectangle
我们已经见到过的矩形检测
Text. Here's another one with
文本  这个是
barcode detection.
条形码检测
And object tracking.
还有对象追踪
And many, many more things.
还有很多很多别的东西
And one of those is actually the
其中一个就是
integration between Vision and
Vision 和 Core ML 的
Core ML.
整合
And that allows you to bring
这会让你自己的
your own machine learning and
机器学习和
computer vision models and run
计算机影像模型
them as part of Vision's
把它们作为 Vision 的
imaging, image processing
图像处理途径的一部分
pipeline so that we can extend
来运行  这样我们就能
our vision framework in very
以非常新奇的方式扩展我们的
novel ways.
影像框架
And to show you an example of
为了给大家展示相关案例
this, I'm going to invite Emily
我想请 Emily Kim 上台
Kim up on stage that will show
请她给我们
you, show us a great demo app.
展示一个很棒的演示 app
Emily?
Emily
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Hi. I'd like to show all of
&gt;&gt;  嗨  我想给大家展示一个
you a demo app that we've
演示 app 我们写这个 app
written to showcase three of the
是为了展示 3 个 iOS 11 的
new technologies in iOS 11 --
最新技术
Core ML, Vision, and Depth.
Core ML Vision 和 Depth
Now, I've asked Seb to help me
我要请 Seb 在这个演示中
out a little bit in this demo,
帮我一把
so it looks like he's just about
看上去他快要准备好了
All right.
好的
So first, we're going to launch
首先  我们要打开这个
the application.
应用
You can see here that the app
你们可以看到
has recognized that Seb is
这个 app 识别出 Seb
holding a piano keyboard, and
拿着一个钢琴键盘
we've placed a speech bubble
于是就在他的嘴边
next to his mouth with a little
放了一个气泡
piano emoji inside.
里面是一个钢琴的 emoji
Now, let's take a quick photo.
咱们快速照张相
And, well, I guess that's a
好了  这就是一张
picture of Seb holding a
Seb 拿着键盘的
keyboard.
照片
I hate to break it to you, Seb,
我不想这么说 Seb
but you look a little boring.
但你看上去有点呆
Can we maybe try something else?
我们可以试试别的吗
&gt;&gt; All right.
&gt;&gt;  好的
&gt;&gt; I mean that in the kindest
&gt;&gt;  我这么说可是
way possible.
绝无冒犯之意
All right.
好吧
Let's see if our app can
咱们看看你的 app
recognize something that's not
是否认出键盘之外的
piano.
东西
So we'll go back.
我们会回来的
All right.
好的
We can see now that Seb's
我们现在看到 Seb
holding a guitar.
拿着一把吉他
The app knows this and has
app 知道这一点
placed a little guitar emoji in
于是它就把一个吉他 emoji
the speech bubble next to his
放在了他嘴边的气泡里
mouth.
咱们再照张相
Whoa, Seb, you look way cooler
哇  Seb 你看上去
than you did before.
比刚才酷多了
You've got some--
你有一些酷酷的气质
[ Laughter ]
[ 笑声 ]
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Yeah, if you'll notice, he's got
是的  如果你注意到了
some cool rock star sunglasses
他被加上了很酷的摇滚明星墨镜
and some cheering fans behind
后面还多了一些欢呼的粉丝
him, so before we jump over to
在我们跳转到
Xcode to take a look at just how
Xcode 上看看
easy it was to write an
写一个让 Seb 都能变酷的 app
application that can make even
有多么简单之前
Seb look cool, let's please give
咱们先为 Seb 鼓掌
a round of applause for Seb for
感谢他的
being a good sport.
大度精神
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
All right.
好的
So this was a pretty standard
这是个标准的
UIKit and AVFoundation
UIKit 和 AVFoundation
application, so I'm not going to
应用  所以我就不多去
go over the details of that.
讲它的细节了
Instead, I'd like to focus on
我想主要讲一讲
the three new areas that you
你们看到的三个新地方
saw: object classification, face
对象分类
landmark detection, and Depth.
面部特征点识别  和景深
So first, let's take a look at
首先  我们先来看看
object classification.
对象分类
Using the power of Core ML, you
借助 Core ML 的力量
can now integrate trained
你可以把经过训练的
machine learning models into
机器学习模型整合到
your app.
你的 app 里
Now, many of you will probably
你们很多人可能会去
be rolling your own.
使用你们自己的
However, we wanted to show you
但我们还是想给你们展示一下
just how easy this was, so we
这有多么容易
simply took an off-the-shelf
所以我们只是拿来一个现成的
model and dropped it into our
模型  并把它放到我们的
project.
项目里
Super easy.
超级简单
You can see here that all we had
你们可以看到
to do was load this model file
我们只需要把这个文件模型
in Core ML and then pass that
加载到 Core ML 里
along to Vision so that we could
再传到 Vision 上面
run this against images.
就能把它运行到图像上
Now, as the frames come in from
相机预览的各帧出现时
the Camera preview, we simply
我们只需要建立一个
create a Core ML request to run
Core ML 请求  让它
on each of these frames.
在每一帧上运行就可以了
Once we recognize an object --
一旦我们识别出了某个对象
for example, the guitar -- the
比如那把吉他
results come back from this
这个请求的返回的结果
request indicating that it's
就会提示它在场景中
found a guitar in the scene, and
发现了一把吉他
then we can place that little
然后我们就可以
guitar emoji inside the speech
把那个吉他 emoji 放在气泡里了
Now, if you also recall from the
大家记得  在刚才的演示中
demo, the speech bubble was
气泡是放在 Seb
placed right next to Seb's
的嘴角旁边的
So how did, how exactly did we
那么我们是怎么知道
know where to put that?
该把气泡放在哪里的呢
Let's take a look at the face
我们来看一看面部
landmark detector.
特征点识别器
Using Vision, you can now find
你可以利用 Vision
the face landmarks, which
找到面部特征点
include for each of your eyes,
包括你的两只眼睛
your nose, and what we're
鼻子  还有我们最感兴趣的地方
interested in, which was the
也就是嘴巴
So again, we simply create a
我们只需要再次建立
face landmarks request and run
一个面部特征点请求
that on the frames that are
然后在相机发来的
coming in from the camera.
帧上面运行
When the request comes back and
请求返回并表示
says that it's found landmarks
它在面部找到了
on a face, we simply ask for
特征点  然后我们就只需要
where the mouth was and then we
去问  嘴巴在哪里
can anchor the speech bubble
然后就能把气泡放在合适位置
appropriately so that it looks
让它看上去
like it's coming out of Seb's
就好像从 Seb 的嘴巴里出来一样
We also used face landmarks to
我们还使用面部特征点
find each of Seb's eyeballs to
找到 Seb 的每只眼球
figure out where to put the
以此确定要把
sunglasses on his face in that
那张吉他酷照中的墨镜
cool guitar photo.
放在他脸上的什么地方
Now, also in that photo, if you
同样是在那张照片里
remember, we replaced the
大家记得  我们换掉了背景
background and put it in front
让他站到了一群
of his adoring fans.
粉丝的前面
So we used Depth to do that, and
我们利用景深做到这一点
let's take a closer look.
我们来深入看一下
So it's really easy to get Depth
现在在你用相机
data now when you capture images
拍摄图像后  很容易能得到
on the camera, so all you have
景深数据
to do once you've captured the
你们中拍摄图像后需要
image is extract that Depth
提取景深信息
information, and then we wrote a
我们写了一个
custom kernel to simply apply
定制的内核
that Depth information to the
把景深信息
captured image in order to
使用在拍摄的图像上
teleport Seb into his rock star
把 Seb 传送到摇滚巨星的世界去
So I hope you've seen just how
我希望大家已经明白
easy it is to incorporate Core
在你们的 app 上使用
ML, Vision, and Depth into your
Core ML Vision 和 Depth
applications.
是多容易了
Back to you, Seb.
交还给你 Seb
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; I have to say that rock star
&gt;&gt;  我必须得说
universe was pretty exciting for
在那几分钟里
the couple minutes I got to live
摇滚巨星的世界
in it.
感觉真爽
So thank you, Emily.
谢谢 Emily
That was really great.
很棒的演示
Now, let's look at Core ML more
让我们再来深入看看
closely.
Core ML
Core ML is really about helping
Core ML 实际上是
you create new experiences in
帮助你在你的 app 里
your app by making it easy for
建立新的体验
you to incorporate machine
让你很容易利用
learning models.
机器学习模型
And so your application can make
这样你的应用就可以
use of domain specific
利用特定领域的
frameworks.
框架了
We've seen Vision.
我们已经看到了 Vision
We also have natural language
还有自然语言
processing.
处理
Or directly use the machine
或者直接使用
learning framework.
机器学习框架
Now, all of this is powered by
所有这些都得到
Accelerate and Metal Shaders to
Accelerate 和 Metal Shaders 的助力
really give you the best
真的会给你
possible performance.
最好的性能
Core ML itself provides a rich
Core ML 本身就提供
set of primitives to integrate
丰富的原语
state-of-the-art machine
来把当前最新的机器学习
learning models into your apps.
模型整合到你的 app 中
We've seen some of those this
我们今天上午已经了解过了
So in addition to supporting
除了支持广泛的
extensive deep learning models
超过 30 层的深度学习模型
with over 30 layers, it supports
它还支持
standard machine learning
标准机器学习模型
models, like tree ensembles,
比如树状集成
SVMs, generalized linear models.
SVM 和广义线性模型等等
Really, the point of this is to
这样的目的是
allow you to target a broad
让你能够把它用在
variety of applications, from
很多类型的应用上
handwriting recognition.
包括手写识别
We talk about image
图像分类
classification, music tagging,
音乐标签
handwriting recognition, and
手写识别
much, much more.
等等很多类型的应用
Many, many other domains are
其他的域也有很多能
available to you.
为你所用
Now, how do you get the models?
你们要如何获得这些模型呢
Well, we give you access to this
我们让你们能够通过
great machine learning community
Turi Caffe 和 Keras 等工具
with tools such as Turi, Caffe,
访问机器学习群落
or Keras, which is a popular
Keras 是 TensorFlow 的一个
library for TensorFlow.
流行的图书馆
Now, what does your work flow
作为开发者
look like as a developer?
你们的工作流是怎样的呢
Well, let's say that you train
比如你用 Caffe
your own models using Caffe, or
训练你自己的模型
perhaps, as Emily did, you pick
或者也许像 Emily 那样
a pre-trained model that's
从网上选择一个
available on the Internet.
预先训练过的模型
You then take that model and run
然后在 Converter 工具中
it through the Converter tool,
运行那个模型
and that Converter tool will
那个 Converter 工具
produce a Core ML compatible
产生一个可在 Core ML 兼容的
format.
格式
You take that, you drag it into
然后把它拖拽到
Xcode, and then you simply start
Xcode 里  然后就可以轻松地
using it in your application.
开始在你的应用里使用它了
Now, we're also open sourcing
我们还开放了
the Core ML Converter tool so
Core ML Converter 工具的源代码
that we can get even broader
这样在未来它就能
community adoption over time.
更广泛地被使用了
We're also focused on
我们还注重性能表现
performance so that it runs
因此它在设备上
great on device.
运行良好
Examples of what we do: graph
我们做的包括
optimizations and fusing
图形优化以及
multiple operations together
自动将多个操作融合到一起
And we also automatically
我们还自动分析
analyze your neural network to
你的神经网络
make best use of hardware
以便更好地利用
acceleration.
硬件加速
So when you bring all of this
把所有这些加在一起
together, Core ML really allows
Core ML 会真的让你能够
you to easily leverage the power
轻松地利用机器学习的力量
of machine learning to create
制作出真正智能的
truly intelligent applications.
应用
It's simple to use, it delivers
它使用简便
great performance and efficiency
在我们所有的平台上
across all of our platforms, and
性能良好  效率很高
it really lets you target your
它真的能够让你把你的
next-generation intelligent app
下一代智能 app
at all, at hundreds of millions
用在数以亿计的
of devices that are Core ML
利用 Core ML 的设备上
enabled.
我们已经迫不及待地想
what you're going to create with
看到你们使用它
this along many of the other
以及我们今天讲到的
APIs that we've talked about
众多其他 API 创造出的成果
So with that, I'd like to call
接下来  我想请
up Jeremy Sandmel up on stage to
Jeremy Sandmel 上台
talk about Metal and graphics.
来讲一讲 Metal 和graphics
Jeremy?
Jeremy
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Seb.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Seb
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Thanks, Seb.
谢谢 Seb
So we developed Metal to be the
我们开发了Metal
fastest and most efficient way
它驱动我们的 iOS
to drive the incredibly powerful
是 macOS 和 tvOS 产品上
GPUs in our iOS, macOS, and tvOS
性能超强的 GPU 最高效的方式
And since its introduction,
推出它之后
we've dramatically expanded
我们极大地扩展了
Metal to support the advanced
Metal 支持先进的
rendering, graphics, and compute
渲染  制图  以及其他
features most requested by our
开发者呼声最高的计算特性
And the results have been
其结果是非常惊人的
There are more than 143,000
在 iOS App Store 里有超过
Metal apps in the iOS App Store
143000 个开发者的
created by our developers who
app 它们可以直接调用
are directly calling the Metal
Metal API
API.
但我们同时也在
system frameworks on top of
Metal 上构建着自己的系统框架
You've heard about a number of
你们今天已经了解过
them today.
其中一些了
For instance, if you're drawing
比如  如果你在用
your user interface with UIKit
UIKit 绘制用户界面
or your maps with MapKit, you're
或者用 MapKit 绘制地图
also using Metal.
那么你其实就在使用 Metal
In fact, over 1.7 million apps
实际上  在 App Store 中
are in the App Store using Metal
有超过170万个 app
through Apple system frameworks
通过 Apple 系统框架使用 Metal
and benefitting from Metal's
并且自动从
performance and power
Metal 的性能和
efficiencies automatically.
功效中获益
Developers are using Metal in
开发者把 Metal 用在了
truly awe-inspiring ways, such
非常了不起的地方
as the professional image and
比如 Serif Labs
photo editing in the new
就在 iPad 上的新
Affinity Photo for iPad from
Affinity Photo 中的图像和照片编辑中
Serif Labs.
用到了它
And 3D modeling and rendering in
还有 MAXON 即将发布的
MAXON's upcoming Cinema 4D with
Cinema 4D 就采用了
AMD's Metal accelerated
AMD的 Metal 加速的 ProRender 技术
ProRender technology.
进行专业 3D 建模和渲染
The gorgeous sci-fi adventure
还有精彩的科幻冒险游戏
game Obduction from Cyan, the
“Obduction” 制作者是 Cyan 公司
legendary creators of the game
也就是游戏 “Myst” 的制作者
And the truly stunning F1 2016
还有 Feral Interactive 公司
racing game from Feral
制作的精彩的赛车游戏
Interactive.
“F1 2016”
In fact, Ian Bullock of Feral
实际上 Feral 的 Ian Bullock
has said that, "Metal's richer
说过 Metal 更丰富的
feature set and lower overhead
特性和更低的系统开销
have allowed them to bring
让他们能够把最新的游戏
cutting edge games to the Mac
带入 Mac 其所达到的
with frame rates and effects
帧率和效果是
that simply weren't possible
以前不可能实现的
Metal is broadly supported
2013 年起  Metal 就得到了
across i, our iOS devices since
iOS 设备的广泛支持
2013 and our Macs since 2012.
在 Mac 设备上更早  2012 年就这样了
And this means there are more
这意味着
than 900 million products
现在有超过 9 亿个产品
supporting Metal across macOS,
支持 Metal 包括 macOS
iOS, and tvOS.
iOS 和 tvOS 等系统
This is truly stunning, and
这真的很惊人
that's why we're so incredibly
因此我们今天
excited today to announce the
非常激动  因为我们要发布
next generation of Metal, Metal
Metal 的下一代 Metal 2 了
Now, Metal 2 is made up of six
Metal 2 有6大关键
key advancements that we're
提升  今天我们要
going to describe to you today.
一一为大家讲解
The first is GPU-driven
首先是 GPU 驱动的
rendering.
渲染
This means that we're continuing
这意味着我们会继续
to reduce the amount of work
减少 CPU 要求的
required by the CPU in order to
工作量
execute your GPU commands.
以便执行你的 GPU 命令
Now, you may recall that the
你也许记得
overhead of OpenGL could often
OpenGL 的系统开销
steal a major portion of your
可能会占据你 app 的
app's per-frame rendering time,
每帧渲染时间中的大部分
significantly limiting your
这会严重限制
application's performance.
你们的应用的性能
And Metal dramatically reduced
而 Metal 会大幅减少
that CPU time, giving it back to
CPU 时间  把时间还给
your application.
你的应用
Well, with Metal 2, we're going
有了 Metal 2 我们会在这方面
even further.
更进一步
We've introduced a number of new
我们已经推出了一些
features designed to off-load
新特性  尽可能地
the CPU as much as possible and
减轻 CPU 的负担
to allow the GPU to much more
让 GPU 去更高效地
efficiently schedule its own
计划它自己的工作
One of these features is called
其中一个特性叫做
Metal argument buffers.
Metal 参数缓冲
Now, as a little bit of
稍微讲一下背景
background, Metal render passes
Metal 渲染通道
are made of graphic state and
是由图形状态和
references to resources, such as
对资源的引用构成的
textures and buffers.
比如纹理和缓冲器
And these resources
这些资源在以前
traditionally needed to be
在每次 draw call 时
specified individually with each
都需要单独被指明
With Metal 2, you can assign
有了 Metal 2 你就可以
your resources to argument
在 app 初始化时
buffers once during your app's
把你的资源分配到
initialization, and then you can
参数缓冲区
rapidly switch between these
然后你可以快速在
argument buffers that you've
根据每次 draw call
already set up with each draw
已经设置好的资源缓冲区之间切换
call, which can be dramatically
这会极大地提高
more efficient.
效率
In fact, the more resources you
实际上  你用到越多的资源
use, the more complex your
你的渲染越复杂
rendering, the greater the
节省的时间
savings can be.
就会越多
And in this example using Metal
在这个用到 Metal
argument buffers, we reduced the
参数缓冲区的例子中
CPU time required for our draw
我们减少了 draw call 所需的
calls by more than 10x.
CPU 时间  多达十倍
Next, Metal 2 has taken major
接下来 Metal 2
steps forward towards a common
在遍布我们各种产品的
feature set across our product
标准特性上  迈出了一大步
We've strongly emphasized
我们在强调
compatibility across our
各平台兼容性的同时
platforms while still providing
仍然为开发者提供了
developers with access to
访问硬件特性
hardware specific features
以获得优化性能
required for optimal
的机会
We're bringing key features from
我们把 macOS 的关键特性
macOS to iOS and vice versa.
带到了 iOS 上  反过来也一样
One of these examples is called
其中一个例子就是
Metal Resource Heaps.
Metal Resource Heaps
This can provide a much more
它可以提供
efficient way of managing your
更高效的办法来管理我们的
Metal textures and buffers
Metal 纹理和缓冲区
without requiring you to become
而不必要求你
an expert in how each individual
懂得每一个独立的 GPU
GPU manages and allocates
是如何管理和分配
memory.
内存的
Traditionally, each Metal
此前  每一个 Metal
texture would require a
纹理都需要操作系统
separate, individual memory
单独分配
allocation from the OS.
一个独立的内存
Now, this was simple to use.
这是很容易使用
It's simple to understand but
很容易理解
could be quite expensive.
但可能会很昂贵
But with Metal Heaps, you can
有了 Metal Heaps
allocate a single memory buffer
你可以分配一个单独的内存缓冲
and then store multiple textures
然后在里面存储多个纹理
You can also do incredibly fast
你还可以非常快地
reallocations and you can
重新分配
reinterpret existing memory for
并为新的纹理重新解读
a new texture.
已有的内存
Interestingly, Metal Heaps also
有趣的是 Metal Heaps
allows you to reuse previously
允许你重新使用
allocated memory from textures
你暂时不需要的纹理中
you don't need simultaneously,
已经被分配的内存
which can save you significant
这可以帮你节省
amounts of memory per frame.
大量的每帧内存
This is all very simple and easy
这非常简单
and doesn't sacrifice any
而且不会牺牲任何
performance.
性能
Now, Metal is not just for
Metal 不仅适用于
graphics.
图形
The Metal Performance Shaders
Metal Performance Shaders Library
Library provides an optimized
提供了一整套优化的
set of image processing, linear
图像处理  线性代数
algebra, and other compute
以及其他计算操作方法
And Metal 2 extends this support
Metal 2 扩展了这种支持
for accelerating machine
以加速机器学习
We've included a number of
我们为卷积码神经网络
GPU-accelerated machine learning
加入了很多
primitives and new graph API for
GPU 加速的机器学习
convolutional neural networks,
原语和新的图像 API
and it can all be efficiently
所有这些都可以高效地
integrated into your Metal
整合到你们的 Metal
graphics and compute code.
图形和计算代码中去
Machine learning kernels such as
机器学习内核
LSTMs, convolutions, and neuron
比如 LSTMs 卷积码和
layers are included as well as
神经元也包括在内
an expanded set of matrix math
还有扩展的矩阵数学操作
And most importantly, MPS also
最重要的是 MPS 也
enables everyone using the
让每个人能够使用
powerful, new Core ML framework
Seb 刚才提到的
that Seb just described to get
强力的  新的 CoreML 框架
the full performance of the GPU
来获得 GPU 的全部性能
for machine learning
以供自动机器学习
Next, we're very excited to talk
接下来  我们很想说一说
about VR in Metal 2.
Metal 2 里的虚拟现实
With Metal 2 and macOS High
有了 Metal 2 和 macOS 的 High
Sierra, we're enabling VR
Sierra  我们会让 Mac
content development on the Mac
第一次具有
for the first time with
VR 内容开发功能
optimized support for 360-degree
包括 360 度视频编辑
video editing and 3D content
和 3D 内容制作
And we've added support for
我们还添加了对
low-latency stereoscopic
头戴显示
rendering on head-mounted
低延迟立体渲染
displays and powerful, new
的支持  以及强大
developer tools to optimize your
的新开发工具  优化
VR app's performance.
VR app 的性能
We're incredibly excited to say
我们很高兴
we've been working closely with
能与 Valve 一起
Valve, and they've announced
密切合作  他们已经宣布
they're bringing their full
他们要把全部的
SteamVR runtime and SDK to the
SteamVR runtime 和 SDK 带到
Mac with beta versions available
Mac 上 beta 版本今天就可以
today.
获得
Yeah.
没错
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
This also includes support for
也包括 HTC Vive
the HTC Vive headset and
头戴设备和手柄
And as you saw this morning,
大家今天上午了解过了
we've also been partnering with
我们也和
Epic Games, who's announced
Epic Games 合作了
macOS VR support in Unreal
他们也宣布今年
Engine in their upcoming release
晚些时候发行的虚幻引擎
later this year with early
将支持 macOS VR
access available from GitHub
9月份就可以在 GitHub 上面
starting in September.
提早访问
This includes support for Epic's
包括支持 Epic 的
immersive VR Mode Editor that
沉浸式 VR Mode Editor
you saw this morning, allowing
大家上午见到过了
you to step inside the VR
你可以身临其境地
environments as you're creating
创造 VR 环境
We're also very excited to be
我们也很高兴能与
partnering with Unity, who has
Unity 进行合作
announced they too are adding
他们同样宣布将
macOS VR support to their
把 macOS VR 支持
incredibly powerful engine and
加入他们超强的引擎
editing environment behind many
以及很多最流行游戏
of the most popular games.
背后的编辑环境
This has enabled the developer
还让开发者
I-Illusions to use Unity to
I-Illusions 使用 Unity
bring the addictive and exciting
令人欲罢不能的
VR space game Space Pirates
VR 太空游戏 Space Pirates
Trainer to the Mac in just a
Trainer 在未来几天内
matter of just a few days.
Mac 上会支持
Now, a word about performance,
现在说一下性能
which is incredibly important
性能对于构建
for building compelling VR apps.
出色的 VR app 来说至关重要
Many developers are familiar
很多开发者都知道
with optimizing their
要把他们的应用
applications to fit within 60
优化到符合
frames per second, and this
每秒60帧的帧率
would mean you would have a
这意味着
fairly generous 16.7
你在每帧可以有
milliseconds per frame all
足足 16.7 毫秒的时间
devoted to your application's
供你的 app
rendering.
渲染
However, to create an immersive
但是  要制造出
VR experience, you need to
沉浸式的 VR 体验
render a full stereoscopic pair
你必须渲染出立体的
of views at 90 frames a second,
两幅视图  帧率要达到 90 帧每秒
which can leave you only about
这就意味着每帧的时间
11 milliseconds per frame.
只有 11 毫秒了
But actually, you don't even get
但实际上  你甚至
all of that quite all to
无法全用上这 11 毫秒
yourself because there's a VR
因为还有 VR compositor
compositor in the mix, which
它要使用 GPU
uses the GPU to combine the
叠加左右眼图像
left- and right-eye images to
补偿 HMD
compensate for HMD lens
镜片的扭曲失真
distortion and for head
还要补偿头部运动
And this leaves you only about
这就只留给你
ten milliseconds per frame.
大约每帧 10 毫秒的时间了
In other words, you need to
换句话说  你需要
target your VR app to achieve
让你的 VR app 达到
100 frames per second.
每帧 100 秒的帧率
Now, this can be very
这是个极具挑战性的工作
challenging, but Metal 2
但是 Metal 2 提供了一些
provides some awesome, new tools
非常强大的新工具
for optimizing your VR app's
优化你的 VR app 的
performance.
性能
We've include built-in support
我们在 Metal system trace 里
for SteamVR's compositor
内置了对于 SteamVR 的 compositor
tracepoints within the Metal
跟踪点的支持
This allows you to see exactly
这会让你能够看到
where the GPU time is going and
GPU 时间都去了哪里
precisely when your frames will
以及你的帧到达屏幕的
hit the glass.
精确时刻
With Metal 2 and the powerful,
有了 Metal 2
new GPUs in the latest iMacs
和即将于今天发布的
that we announced that we're
新 iMac 里的
shipping today, we fully enabled
强大的新 GPU
VR content development on your
我们让你们的 Mac 桌面
Mac desktop.
VR 内容开发大有用武之地
Now, many professional content
很多专业的
creators love the mobility of
内容生产者都很喜欢
working with our MacBook Pros,
MacBook Pro 带来的移动办公便利
but intensive VR development can
但大量的 VR 开发
require powerful GPUs that don't
需要强劲的 GPU
always fit in the thinnest and
它很难能被装在
lightest laptops.
最轻最薄的笔记本上
This is why Metal 2 is bringing
因此 Metal 2 会
first-class support for external
为你们的 MacBook Pro
GPUs to your MacBook Pro and to
和 macOS High Sierra 外接 GPU
macOS High Sierra.
提供一流支持
Yeah, thanks [applause].
是的  谢谢 [ 掌声 ]
So you could very easily add
你们可以非常轻松地
support to your app for external
用外接 GPU 给你们的 app 提供支持了
GPUs.
只需要几行代码
code, and you register for
你要记录外接 GPU
external GPU device connection
设备连接回调函数
callbacks and identify which
并指明
GPUs in your system are
你的系统中的哪些 GPU
removable.
是可移除的
This enables the best of both
这样就两全其美了
worlds -- the GPU horsepower for
可以用强劲的 GPU
building immersive VR
在我们最便携的 Mac 设备上
applications on our most mobile
构建沉浸式 VR app 了
Macs -- and we're really excited
我们对此非常兴奋
So to get you started, we're
为帮你们尽快上手
offering an external GPU
我们会在开发者计划中
Developer Kit through our
提供一个外部 GPU
Developer program.
Developer kit
It includes everything you need
里面包括你在 MacBook Pro 上
for VR content development on
进行 VR 内容开发
your MacBook Pro, including a
所需要的一切
discount on the HTC Vive
还包括 HTC Vive
head-mounted display, and it's
头戴显示的优惠
all available today from
今天就可以在
developer.apple.com.
developer.apple.com 上获得
And last but not least, Metal 2
最后要说的是 Metal 2
enables and provides our most
让我们有了
advanced graphics developer
最先进的图像开发
optimization tools yet.
优化工具
We've added the top-requested
我们添加了呼声最高的
tools and features to enable
工具和特性
rapid debugging, analysis, and
包括快速 debug 分析和
optimization of your GPU
优化你的 GPU
performance bottlenecks.
性能瓶颈
And it's all integrated directly
所有这些都直接
into Xcode and Instruments.
内置在 Xcode 和 Instruments 里
We've included powerful, new GPU
我们添加了强有力的新
hardware performance and
GPU 硬件性能
software performance counters,
和软件性能计数器
giving you deep insight into the
让你们深入了解
GPU's operation and automatic
GPU 的操作和自动
bottleneck detection that can
瓶颈检测
take you exactly to the source
让你直达性能问题的
of your performance problems.
核心源头
It's all very powerful.
非常强大
And to show you a demo of Metal
接下来要为大家展示
2 Developer tools in action, I'd
Metal 2 开发工具的应用
like to invite Eric Sunnel
我想请 Eric Sunnel
[phonetic] to the stage.
上台
Eric?
Eric
&gt;&gt; Jeremy.
&gt;&gt;  Jeremy
Thanks Jeremy.
谢谢 Jeremy
Hi, everyone.
大家好
Today I'd like to show you a
今天我想给你们展示
couple of the new features in
一些 Metal 的新特性
Metal, like our GPU profile
比如 Xcode 里的 GPU 资料
counter tool in Xcode.
计数器工具
So what I have here is a Metal
屏幕上是一个 Metal 应用
application rendering thousands
正在渲染数以千计的
of asteroids on the screen.
小行星
And it's, all is individual draw
每一个都是独立的 draw call
calls, and it's important to
需要注意的是
note that each of these draw
每一个 draw call
calls is using a number of
都在使用一些
unique Metal resources all
独一无二的 Metal 资源
chosen at runtime.
都是随机选择的
So now what I'm going to do here
现在我要做的是
is add a couple more asteroids
向场景中再添加一些
to the scene.
小行星
All right, that's not performing
好的  现在情况不如
quite as well as I want, so
我预想的顺利
let's exit out of full screen,
我们退出全屏
and take a GPU capture, and see
做一个 GPU 捕捉
if we can get a better idea of
看看是否能更好地理解
what's going on.
发生了什么
So not only is it taking a GPU
它不仅是做了一个 GPU
capture and analyzing all of our
捕捉  并分析我们所有的
shaders, but now it's also
着色器  它还捕捉了
capturing all of the hardware
所有的硬件性能
performance counters and
计数器
actually on a per draw call
它实际上在每个 draw call
basis.
都这样做一次
It'll be able to visualize that
它可以很快就把这
in a second.
视觉化
All right, so now on the
好了  现在在左边
left-hand -- actually, let me
让我更改一下
change my system editor here.
系统编辑器
And on the left-hand side, now I
在左手边
have access to a GPU report that
我可以访问一份 GPU 报告
now brings up in the standard
它在标准编辑器里
editor a summary of all the
总结出了所有的
performance counters on the
在所有 draw call 的时间线上的
timeline for all of the draw
性能计数器
And on the right-hand side, I
而在右手边
have all the detailed
我也有所有的
performance counters as well.
详细的性能计数器
So if I select a particular draw
如果我选择了一个特定的
call -- let's say this one for
draw call 比如这个吧
instance -- all of the
所有的右边的
right-hand side updates with all
信息都会更新
the detailed performance
显示出我们捕捉的
counters that we've captured.
详细的性能计数器
If I hover over the vertices
如果我在 vertices 行上面悬停
row, here I can get an idea of,
我就能够了解
OK, what's the summary for that
那个 vertice 的 draw call
draw call for the vertices
提交到场景的
submitted to the scenes?
总数是多少
Almost 8000.
差不多有 8000
Seems pretty high.
看上去挺高的
If I look at the pixels stored,
如果我去查看存储的像素
it looks like I'm only storing
在那个 draw call 上
about 11 pixels for that draw
我只存储了大约 11 个像素
call, which seems a lot lower in
比起来就低多了
So now, if we look in the upper
如果我们看右边的上部
right-hand side, we can see some
我们能够看到
of the recommendations provided
Xcode 提供的一些
by Xcode.
建议
The top one here, pixels per
最上面的这个
triangle ratio, is very low.
每三角形像素比  是很低的
Seems about right.
看上去没什么问题
Now, if we disclose this, we get
如果我们打开这个
some of the recommendations made
就能得到一些 Xcode 的建议
So we can see here it says,
我们可以看到这里它说
"Consider reducing the number of
考虑减少三角形的数量
triangles and consider reducing
并考虑减少
the work in the vertex shader."
顶点着色点的工作
Now, if we click on the top one
如果我们点击顶部
and click on the link here,
点击这里的链接
it'll take us right to all the
它会让我们看到
bound resources for the draw
这个 draw call 的所有捆绑
call.
资源
We can see here that we're
我们能看到
actually loading our high poly
我们实际上是加载了
model of the asteroid, which
小行星的高精度模型
doesn't make much sense for this
这在这个场景下没什么意义
So we're going to go over here
所以我们要
and make a source code change.
改写一个源代码
Get rid of the editor.
退出编辑器
All right.
好了
And let's change this to the
我们把这个改成
reduced model that I've prepared
我之前准备的
ahead of time.
降阶模型
All right.
好了
Now, let's make one more change
现在  我们在这个项目里
in this project.
再做一个改变
Let's see if we can make useful
看看我们是否能让参数缓冲区
argument buffers.
起作用
So what I have here is our for
这里是 for 循环
loop that's making, that's doing
它在做每个小行星的
the per draw call for each
draw call
And above each draw call, I'm
在每个 draw call 之上
setting a number of resources.
我设定了一系列资源
So with argument buffers, I can
有了参数缓冲
remove this code and, instead,
我就能删除这个代码
insert a call to binding our
换以插入一个调用
argument buffer ahead of time
预先捆绑参数缓冲
and basically allow the GPU now
允许 GPU 制作
to make the dynamic selection of
动态选择  决定
which resources to use.
使用哪些资源
So with these two simple changes
做好了这两个简单的更改后
in place, let's run and see
我们运行一下
where our performance is now.
看看怎么样了
All right.
好的
OK, that's looking good.
好的  看上去不错
Let's add some more.
我们再加一些
OK, that's looking a lot better.
好的  看上去好多了
That's exactly what I like to
我想看的就是这个
see.
好  就是这样
the new features in Metal 2, we
有了 Metal 2 的新特性
hope you get deeper insight into
我希望你们能够更加深入
where your application is
了解你们的应用把时间
spending time, and we'll offer
都花在哪里了  我们还会
even more code from the critical
从关键路径上提供更多
path.
代码
Thanks very much.
非常感谢
Back to you, Jeremy.
轮到你了 Jeremy
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Well, thanks, Eric.
&gt;&gt;  好的  谢谢 Eric
So that's Metal 2 -- GPU-driven
这就是 Metal 2 GPU 驱动的
rendering, a unified feature
缓冲  一体化特性平台
platform, machine learning
机器学习加速
acceleration, support for VR
支持在 Mac 上进行 VR 内容开发
content development on your Mac
支持外接 GPU
with support for external GPUs,
和我们的
and our most advanced developer
最新最先进的
optimization tools to date.
开发者优化工具
We can't wait to see what you're
我们迫不及待地想看到
going to build with Metal next.
你们接下来用 Metal 制作的东西
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
And now, I'd like to invite to
现在  我想请上来
the stage Vice President of AR
AR&VR 技术开发
and VR Technologies, Mike
副总裁 Mike
Rockwell.
Rockwell
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Jeremy.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Jeremy
So I am incredibly excited to
我非常期待和你们
talk to you about ARKit, Apple's
分享 ARKit 这是 Apple 的
new framework that enables the
新框架  它能在
creation of augmented reality
iOS 上制作增强现实
apps on iOS.
应用
One of our primary goals in
我们制作 ARKit 的
creating ARKit was to make sure
目标之一就是确保
we could support a broad range
我们能够从一开始就支持
of devices from day one.
广泛类型的设备
We didn't want to require
我们不想要求
specialized hardware, and I'm
特定的硬件
happy to say that we achieved
我很高兴地说  我们实现了这一点
that.
ARKit 在 iPhone 6s 及升级的设备
and iPad Pro and later.
iPad Pro 及升级的设备上都可以运行
That means it will run on
这意味着它
hundreds of millions of devices
从第一天开始就能在
from day one.
数亿设备上运行
It makes iOS the largest AR
这让 iOS 成为了
platform in the world.
全世界最大的 AP 平台
So what do you need to do to
那么要制作出色的 AR
create great AR?
你们需要做什么呢
The first thing you need to know
你们首先要知道的
is where the camera is in space
就是相机在空间的哪里
and where it's looking.
它又在看哪里
We use a technique called
我们使用了一个名为
visual-inertial odometry to do
视觉惯性里程计的技术实现这一点
that.
我们看看它是怎么完成的
So we've got our scene and we've
我们有场景
got our camera.
还有相机
And the camera's looking at the
相机在看世界
We identify feature points in
我们在世界中确定
the world and we track them from
特性要点  然后一帧一帧地
frame to frame.
追踪它们
From that, we are able to
从那里  我们能够
back-calculate the location of
反算出相机的位置
the camera, and create a
并制造一个
coordinate system, and then give
坐标系  然后
you that location in real time
以 60 帧每秒的帧率
at 60 frames per second.
实时给出那个位置
Now, if we were going to do that
如果要以每秒 60 帧
calculation at 60 frames per
做那个计算
second, it would take a lot of
它会占据很大的
CPU horsepower.
CPU 马力
What we do instead is we fuse
我们没有这样做  而是把
the data from the accelerometer
加速计和陀螺仪的数据
and the gyro with that tracking
与那个追踪信息融合
information and we're able to
这样我们就能够
reduce the compute load
大幅减轻计算负担了
In fact, to get this information
实际上  要获得这个信息
only takes a fraction of a
只需要用到一个 CPU 的
single CPU.
极小一部分
That leaves the GPU available to
这会让 GPU 可以为你所用
you to do fantastic rendering of
完成出色的 3D 对象的
3D objects.
渲染
The second thing you need is to
此外  你还需要
be able to understand the scene.
理解场景
So what's in there so that you
那里有什么
can put things in there and have
这样你才能把东西放进去
them integrate and feel natural.
让它们整合  并很自然
We use those feature points that
我们用之前跟踪的
we tracked earlier to identify
特征要点去识别
major planes in the scene.
场景中的主平面
We look for ones that coplanar,
我们寻找共面的东西
and then we find the extents of
然后我们找到在场景中的
those planes across the scene.
这些平面的范围
That allows you to integrate
你就可以整合对象了
objects and have them be
并让这个过程变得
completely natural.
完全自然
So I can, for example, set that
所以举例来说  我可以
vase on the table, and it feels
把那个花瓶放在桌面上
like it's in the scene itself.
看上去好像本来就在场景里
Now, if you didn't know what the
如果你不知道那张桌子的尺寸
size of the table was, your vase
你的花瓶就可能
might come out and be gigantic.
变得非常巨大
So in addition to identifying
所以在识别平面之外
those planes, we make sure that
我们还要保证
the coordinate system is
坐标系是精确的
accurate.
实际上  误差在
5 percent, so your objects feel
5% 之内  这样你的对象
like that they're natural in the
才会让人感觉它本身就在场景里
The final thing you need in
要让对象
order to enable those objects to
在场景中感觉无违和
feel right in the scene is to
你要做的最后一件事
have the lighting be accurate.
是让光线精准
So we provide accurate light
所以我们提供了
estimations so that as the scene
精确的光线估算
would darken, you can darken
所以在场景变暗时
your objects as well.
你也可以同步把对象变暗
If you don't have that, then
如果没有这个
objects appear to glow in the
物体就会在场景中发光
scene and they won't appear
那就不自然了
So let's look at how you can
我们看一看
access this incredibly powerful
你要如何访问这个超强的
framework.
框架
It's really very easy.
真的很简单
All of this is available through
所有这些都可以从 ARKit 中得到
ARKit.
你只需要建立一个
session configuration, include
会话配置
things like whether you want to
包括你是否想要平面估算
have plane estimation, whether
是否想要光线探测
you want to have a light probe,
等等内容
and then you start an AR
然后你可以开始 AR 会话
Once that's started, your frames
开始后  你可以从
will be either delivered to you
AR 会话委托中
in the AR session delegate or
获取帧  或者
you can access them as a
以 AR 会话属性的方式
property off of the AR session.
访问它们
Each one of those frames
每一帧都包含
contains things like a time
时间印记
stamp, the captured image, the
捕捉的图像
camera direction and position,
相机方向与位置
the major planes in the scene,
场景主平面
and the light probe.
和光线探测等
So now that you've got your
现在你的场景
scene set up, you're ready to
设置完毕  你可以开始渲染了
And ARKit supports a broad range
ARKit 支持
of options for rendering.
渲染的多重选项
You can use Metal 2, as Jeremy
你可以使用刚才 Jeremy
just talked about -- that
说过的 Metal 2
incredibly powerful low-level
它是一个非常强的
engine for accessing the GPU --
访问 GPU 的底层引擎
but you might want to use a
但你可能想要
higher-level framework because
使用高层框架
that's what your abstraction
因为你的抽象化会用到它
So we've optimized both SceneKit
所以我们优化了 SceneKit
and SpriteKit to work with
和 SpriteKit 让它们和
ARKit, and it's very efficient.
ARKit 一起工作  非常高效
In addition, we've been spending
此外  我们在过去几个月里
the last few months partnering
与大型 3D 引擎
with the large 3D engine
供应商合作
providers to make sure that
确保他们的
their engines were optimized for
引擎针对 ARKit 优化过了
And I'm really happy to announce
我非常高兴地宣布
that Unity is releasing an open
Unity 本周将
source plug-in this week that
发布一个开源插件
works just like ARKit, so it's
就像 ARKit 一样
incredibly easy to use.
非常易用
In addition, Epic is releasing
此外  Epic
support in the Unreal Engine so
也将在虚幻引擎中提供支持
that, in a developer preview
在今天的开发者预览中可以看到
today, and they'll be shipping
他们会在今年的晚些时候
it later on this year.
正式发布
So that's a little bit of a
这就是一个预览
preview, a look at ARKit.
看一看 ARKit
I'd like to invite Martin
我想请乐高公司的 Martin
Sanders from LEGO to the stage
Sanders 上台
to give us a little demo of some
向我们演示
of the fun things they've been
他们创造出来的
working on.
有趣的东西
Thank you.
谢谢
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Hi, everybody.
&gt;&gt;  大家好
Great to be here.
很高兴来这里
At LEGO, we've been using ARKit
在乐高  我们用 ARKit
to develop some fun, exciting
开发了一些有趣的
experiences that can bring your
体验  让你们的乐高
LEGO creations to life in
玩具在真实世界中
real-world environments.
获得生命
So it all begins with the
一切都始于
automatic plane detection.
自动平面检测
So as that helicopter moves
这个直升机移动时
around, it gives us that
会给我们一个
surface, and we know we have
表面  我们知道
that surface to start building.
要在这个表面上开始搭建
So let's go ahead and add some
我们先从最近的
sets from our recent collection
“乐高蝙蝠侠大电影”里
and The LEGO Batman Movie.
找些东西添加进去吧
So here we have Arkham Asylum,
这里我们有阿克哈姆疯人院
and with those realistic shadows
有真实的阴影
and that dynamic lighting, it
和动态灯光
really adds that sense of
真的让它栩栩如生
And on top of that, when we put
在此基础上
in things like animations and
我们再加上动画和效果
effects, it really adds that
就会真的再加上
sense of magic and life to them.
一种魔法与生命的感觉
And with size estimation, all of
有了尺寸估算
the sets that we bring in come
我们加进来的玩具
out one-to-one scale, so we know
都是一比一的
that they're actually matching
我们会知道它们和乐高玩具
LEGO sets.
是一样的大小
So this is looking like a cool
这看上去是个很酷的
Gotham City scene, but it
哥谭镇场景
definitely feels like
但总觉得
something's missing, doesn't it?
缺点什么  不是吗
So let's go ahead and add the
所以我们要继续添加
one and only LEGO Batmobile.
独一无二的乐高蝙蝠车
And the man himself, the Caped
还有那个男人
Crusader, LEGO Batman, of
披风斗士  乐高蝙蝠侠  当然
Now, it's a really cool model to
这真是个超酷的
check out.
模型
There's no doubt about it.
毫无疑问
But we can go a little further
但我们可以更进一步
We can start investigating how
我们可以开始调查
models are actually constructed
模型是怎么搭建的
and made by exploring it in this
用这个视图来看一看
Now, Batman doesn't look too
蝙蝠侠似乎不太高兴
happy about this, so let's put
所以我们还是先
that back together for now, I
把它拼回去吧  我想
Now, we also have the power to
我们还能放大
scale up our models.
我们的模型
Now, imagine what it's like when
想像一下  你钻到
you can go inside your LEGO
你的乐高模型内部
creations and explore and view
从全新的角度
them from new perspectives.
观察探索它们
And with the Batmobile at this
有了这么大的蝙蝠车
scale, who wouldn't want to go
谁又不想
inside and check out all the
钻进去一探究竟
cool gadgets and cockpit things
看看那些超酷的装备
from there?
和驾驶舱呢
[applause] And maybe even
[掌声]  甚至还能
involve some friends in there as
从里面看到外面的朋友
well.
什么都行
I don't know.
来张自拍
It's fun stuff.
非常有趣
So as our LEGO sets start to
随着我们的乐高套装
come to life and animate, we can
获得了生命与动态
even then take on the role of
我们甚至可以开始扮演
being the moviemaker.
电影制作者的角色了
So imagine now capturing all of
想象一下  随着我们的进入  把这些场景
those scenes and those epic
和精彩镜头都捕捉下来
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
Full time.
无时无刻
At LEGO, we've been looking into
在乐高  我们研究
augmented reality for quite a
增强现实已经有
few years.
好几年了
Yeah, yeah.
对吧
Pretty epic shot, right?
这个镜头是不是很赞
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
And we've had plenty of ideas in
我们有很多的创意
this space for sure, but it's
但知道现在
only recently with the power and
有了 ARKit 的
ease of ARKit that we can
强大功能与便捷性
finally turn them into reality.
我们才终于把创意变成了现实
So later this year, we are
所以在今年晚些时候
really looking forward to
我们非常期待能够
bringing some of those
把这些体验
experiences to life for you and
在 App Store 中
everyone else in the App Store.
带给你们和每一个人
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; All right.
&gt;&gt;  好的
Thank you.
谢谢
That was a great demo.
真是精彩的演示
OK, so if you would like to get
如果你想了解
more ideas for how you can
更多关于如何
leverage AR in your own apps, I
在自己的 app 中利用 AR 的创意
recommend that you walk over to
我建议你们走到
our Hands On area that is open
动手体验区  现在已经开放了
now and will be open until 7:00
一直会开到
p.m. tonight.
今晚 7 点
You'll find many more demos
你们会找到更多的
there from partners we've been
演示  来自我们在 AR 领域的
working with on AR.
合作伙伴
And that already brings us to
这就是我们这个
the end of this session.
演讲的全部内容
There are a ton of new
有一大批新的
technologies and APIs here that
技术和 API
you should get your hands on.
你们都应该体验一下
We are enabling entirely new
我们让全新类型的
types of applications and we're
应用变得可能
providing you with building
我们为你们提供了
blocks for forward-looking
前沿技术的开发基石
technologies like machine
如机器学习
learning and augmented reality.
和增强现实
So go take a closer look and see
所以请更深入了解
how we can leverage these for
我们怎么利用它们
creating even more compelling
创造更加伟大的 app
apps.
我们所有操作系统
previews for all our operating
和开发者工具的
systems and developer tools will
开发者预览
be available from the WWDC
今天下午在 WWDC
Attendee Portal this afternoon,
Attendee Portal 就可以下载了
so you can take a whole, get a
你们可以立刻
hold of them right away and
得到它们
learn about all the things we
并了解我们发布的东西
And yes, of course, many
是的  当然
sessions here at the conference
大会的很多演讲
that will cover many of these
会更加深入地
topics more deeply, and I also
讲解这些主题
recommend that you make good use
我建议你们好好利用
of the many labs we organize.
我们组织的很多实验室
You can meet the Apple engineers
你们可以在现场
right here on site to answer
见到 Apple 工程师
your questions.
答疑解惑
And with that, I hope you have a
我希望大家享受这次
great conference, and I'll see
盛会  我们本周
you around this week.
还会再见